<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- This is a WordPress eXtended RSS file generated by WordPress as an export of your site. -->
<!-- It contains information about your site's posts, pages, comments, categories, and other content. -->
<!-- You may use this file to transfer that content from one site to another. -->
<!-- This file is not intended to serve as a complete backup of your site. -->

<!-- To import this information into a WordPress site follow these steps: -->
<!-- 1. Log in to that site as an administrator. -->
<!-- 2. Go to Tools: Import in the WordPress admin panel. -->
<!-- 3. Install the "WordPress" importer from the list. -->
<!-- 4. Activate & Run Importer. -->
<!-- 5. Upload this file using the form provided on that page. -->
<!-- 6. You will first be asked to map the authors in this export file to users -->
<!--    on the site. For each author, you may choose to map to an -->
<!--    existing user on the site or to create a new user. -->
<!-- 7. WordPress will then import each of the posts, pages, comments, categories, etc. -->
<!--    contained in this file into your site. -->

<!-- generator="WordPress/3.7.5" created="2014-12-08 20:45" -->
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/excerpt/"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/"
>

<channel>
	<title>Blue Hills Cycling Club</title>
	<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2014 20:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<wp:wxr_version>1.2</wp:wxr_version>
	<wp:base_site_url>http://www.bluehillscycling.com</wp:base_site_url>
	<wp:base_blog_url>http://www.bluehillscycling.com</wp:base_blog_url>

	<wp:author><wp:author_id>1</wp:author_id><wp:author_login>Pedro</wp:author_login><wp:author_email>pedro@bluehillscycling.com</wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[Pedro]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>
	<wp:author><wp:author_id>2</wp:author_id><wp:author_login>Pete</wp:author_login><wp:author_email>pete@bluehillscycling.com</wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[Pete]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>
	<wp:author><wp:author_id>4</wp:author_id><wp:author_login>BHCCAdmin</wp:author_login><wp:author_email>pedro@bluehillscylcing.com</wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[BHCCAdmin]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>


	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.7.5</generator>

	<item>
				<title>Purgatory Road Race - Massachusetts State Road Racing Championships</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=55</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=55</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<br><div><b><i>Bart Lipinski - Masters 35+</i></b></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>After somewhat of a peak two weeks ago at Killington, I was trying to ride it out as long as possible. Trying to rest as much as possible, but not too much as to fall off the edge I was trying to stay on. I was kind of looking forward to this race even though I wasn't sure what to expect. Last year I finished 29th and with guys like Mark McCormack in the field, left me a little further in doubt.</span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>Still wasn't sure during the first lap. Legs were still feeling heavy. </span></div>

<!--more-->

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>I few small breaks, but nothing seemed to last longer than a lap. I was almost sure nothing was going to stick so I buried myself in the group and tried to do as little as possible to save everything for the last climb and field sprint.</span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>The masters 35+ race consists of 5 - 11 miles laps. Each with just over 800' of climbing per lap. The last 1K is almost exactly the same as the Blue Hills service road. 3 steps to the top with a 200M sprint to the finish.</span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>At the end of the 3rd lap two riders got off the front and opened up a sizeable gap. About half way through the 3rd lap two more took off. I'm sure everyone was thinking the same as myself. They aren't going to get caught. Just a little bit further up the (about<span>  </span>3/4's of the way through the 3rd lap), something told me to go. Luckily, no one followed. One and a quarter laps to go and I was trying to bridge a gap to two guys that were trying to do the same. </span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>I did manage to catch the two ahead of me just as they were catching the two leaders. Unfortunately for me I caught them at the base of the big 1K climb (but was able to keep pace with the 4 others). We all worked pretty well together for the last lap. Just before the road started to tilt up for the last 3 or 4 miles, we heard one of the course marshals' yell out "one minute thirty seconds!" I was peaking back from time to time, but was relieved that we were that far ahead and we were not going to get caught.</span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>As we made the last right hander to head straight up, I knew two were going to go and it was going to come down to the a fight for 3rd. I managed to pick the right wheel and followed the 3rd place rider right up to the 50 meter line and flew around him not giving him a chance to get me back. I crossed the line 3rd. And very happy that this one was over. Because the second place rider was from out of state, that moved me to a silver in the state championship. Second to Mark McCormack in the State Championship!!! Thats when it sunk in. Second to an ex-pro and an ex-national champion. I'll take that any day. Well....maybe.</span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>I didn't do much during the race until the last lap and a quarter. For the race I averaged only 221 watts (272 NP) for the 55 miles. </span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>Had a nice big steak and a couple of Harpoons when I got home with the family.....and definitely looking forward to a couple of weeks of rest.</span></div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>55</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-06-11 17:45:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-06-11 17:45:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>purgatory-road-race-massachusetts-state-road-racing-championships</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/06/purgatory-road-race-massachusetts-state.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/4820274894743236562]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>6 Hours of Pats Peak</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=56</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2013 19:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=56</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<br><div><span><b><i>Pete Werner – Solo Men</i></b></span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>When I arrived at Pat’s Peak for the 6 hour endurance race, the rain had just stopped. They received 3 inches of rain in the last 48 hours and the last remaining bit of snow on the mountain had finally melted. The ground was saturated from the snow that was blown all season so the course was going to be extremely muddy.</span></div>

<div><br></div>

<div><span>The race started really fast. The course went up hill immediately. It was very muddy and pretty steep in spots. With all of the congestion, mud and steep turns there was a lot of running, walking and pushing.  My heart rate was well into the 180’s which is not where I want to be in the first 30 minutes of a 6 hour race.</span></div>

<!--more-->

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>The latter half of the course was awesome. The course started to descend back to the base. There were lots of technical rocks and drops to negotiate all with really big puddles on the other side that hid any potential obstacles.</span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>I made a wrong turn on Lap 1, 2 and 3 which cost me a bit of time. I was focusing so hard on staying up right that I just wasn’t paying attention to the course. By Lap 4 I started to settle in. I started to really rock the course and get into the groove. Right about when I started getting comfortable, my small chain ring blew of the bike. I think all of the mud had finally caught up to my drive train. I really needed that chain ring, but now I had to rely on the middle ring.  I am no stranger to standing up an grinding it out but with all of the mud, it was very difficult to get any traction in a 32 tooth chain ring so there was going to be a lot more walking and running next to my bike.</span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>By the end of Lap 4, my rear brake completely failed. This was very problematic and led to me crashing on  a very steep, narrow muddy descent on the end of Lap 4, 5 and 6 (Lap 7 I finally was smart enough to walk it). I think I missed my brake more than the chain ring.  I realized by lap 5 that I was starting to lap a number of riders in my field. This really kept me going and took my mind off of all of the mechanical mishaps that were bringing me down.</span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>I finished with 7 laps which put me in 5<sup>th</sup> place. I was 6 minutes behind 4<sup>th</sup> place. Time to rebuild the bike for the next one. New chain rings, bottom bracket and pads are on order from Landry’s.</span></div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>56</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-06-10 19:48:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-06-10 19:48:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>6-hours-of-pats-peak</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/06/6-hours-of-pats-peak.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/1568972740376455807]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Killington Stage Race</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=57</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=57</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<br><div><span><b><i>Bart Lipinski - Masters 40+</i></b></span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>Ok….here it goes. A quick report on this past weekend’s Killington Stage Race. In as few words as possible.</span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span><b><i>Friday (day before stage 1)</i></b> – Spent way too much time checking the hourly weather reports, but in a weird kind of way was excited about racing Stage 1 with weather in the low 40’s, high winds and rain in the forecast. Not sure why….but I was.</span></div>

<!--more-->

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>Saturday, Stage 1 Circuit Race, 51 miles – 40+’s were scheduled to start at 9:30, but had already changed my mind about racing in today’s weather. Everyone was pretty much soaked as we rolled out to the neutral start. Right off the start, two guys went, but were eventually caught about 20 miles in. At that point I think it’s pretty much safe to say that the entire field wanted this to be over. A safe and cautious ride to the finish.</span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>Luckily for me, I had wrapped my cleats in plastic bags and tapped the hell out of them. Then put shoe covers on over them to hide them. They worked great for the first two laps. On the decent of the last lap, feet were wet and I got that “death chill” that you can’t get rid of. By the end of the race, hands and fingers didn’t work. Finished 17<sup>th</sup>, but had the same time as most of the favorites. Plenty of time to make it up in the next two days.</span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>It took about 15 minutes of sitting in the car with the heat on before I was able to unclick my helmet. Oh yea…..thanks to hypothermia, I could not stop my boy from shaking. Food, drinks and about a half hour helped fix that. Back to the condo to eat and recover.</span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span><b><i>Sunday, Stage 2 Road Race, 62 miles</i></b> – Since we could see the finish line from our window, today’s warm-up was making the 1,500’ decent down East Mountain Road. The forecast for today was looking really good. No rain (haha), but very cold. Only in the upper 40’s-low 50’d for the day. Nothing like racing in the end of May in my winter clothes.</span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>As we rolled up to the start line….rain….again. Was nothing like Saturday, but WTF? We only were about 3 to 4 miles in when two went off the front (and not to be seen again). The race leader had guys trying to real them back in, so we just sat in and let them do all the work (although once again, I did way too much work…haha…surprise). There was a small break (2 guys) at about mile 40. That’s the one I wish I acted on. These 2 finished 2<sup>nd</sup>and 3<sup>rd</sup> on the stage. But I was worried about having enough left in the tank to get back up the mountain.</span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>We got through the first 56 miles in just over two and a half hours. The last five were straight up. 1,500’ that would take almost 25 minutes to get to the top. Luckily I found my rhythm, and got to the top just about as fast as I was hoping to. Shaved over 3 minutes off my best time and crossed the line 11<sup>th</sup>, 2 minutes back from the guys I should have chased. But was very happy that I moved to 11<sup>th</sup>overall in the GC and that Stage 2 was in the books.</span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span><b><i>Monday, Stage 3 Time Trial, 11 miles</i></b> – Finally some sun and bright blue skies. Today’s only issue was the wind. 15 mile an hour winds from the North West. Of course that was the direction we were heading. The finish line was also up about 500’ over the start line. So, a steady 11 mile TT climb, with a head wind. </span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>Today’s plan was simple enough….Make the Podium. This was my chance to really move up in the GC. But right after I left the start, I realized the head wind was not just a head wind. In the valley (Rt. 4/100) it was swirling. Sometimes from the front, or the right. But it would immediately switch to the left or maybe a quick push from behind. With a 80mm front wheel (only mistake I made today), I think I spent more energy trying to hold the bike straight and upright than what was going into the pedals.</span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>The 11 miles went by quickly and before I knew it, I was sprinting with whatever I had left. I was done, it was over. And when the stage and overall GC results went up I could not believe my efforts took me to 2<sup>nd</sup> for the stage and moved me from 11<sup>th</sup>to 6<sup>th</sup> overall in the GC.</span></div>

<div><span><br></span></div>

<div><span>All in all, it was a great weekend to race. Ever with the shitty weather. It was great to stay with Ari for 4 days and to see and hang out with a few other friends….off the bike for once. Next year I’ll be on the final podium….I promise.</span></div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>57</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-05-29 17:05:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-05-29 17:05:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>killington-stage-race</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/05/killington-stage-race.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/151514667029189257]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Sterling Road Race Reports</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=58</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 22:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=58</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<br><div><span><b><i><span> </span>Bart Lipinski - Masters 35+</i></b></span></div>

<p>Ok, so first off, I think I paid way too much attention through out the week to the weather. Rain and thunderstorms were predicted for Saturday all week. I have only done this race once before as a Cat 5 and it was cold and the sky’s opened up. Could not see a thing, so there was always a bad taste in my mouth about this one. Thankfully, the rain held off and there was not much more that a steady drizzle for the last 3 laps. The ground was wet, but at least you could see the road and the potholes. </p>

<!--more-->



<p>Saturday morning was kind of a weird one. I almost didn’t even want to ride my bike, let alone race. There was no doubt that I was racing, just one of those days I felt like doing nothing.</p>



<p>The race, long neutral start to the course and was feeling ok. The first few laps a guy here or there would get out a 30 second lead or so, but this was a lazy group. No one wanted to work and when someone did get off the front, teammates would block (very narrow roads).  Two others did get out for about two laps, but everyone was back together for the last lap.</p>



<p>For most of the race I was focusing on my riding position and being where I though I should be. I almost didn’t even care about the results. Killington is 2 weeks away, the road is slick, figured I’d play it save today.</p>



<p>But….I was able to but myself in a pretty good position. The last ½ mile (about 140’ up) took you into the town square, where with about .1 miles to go, a sharp right and about an 8% sprint up to the finish line. A fast lead out by one team took the pack from a group of about 30 riders to a single file line (coming into the sharp right hander). I was about 9 or 10 wheels back, turned right and dumped what I had left. Picked up all by 3 guys to finish 4</p>



<p>There were a few times I tried to get in a break (didn’t work) or bridge the gap, but other than that, really didn’t do much. I think that I finally figured out how to ride smart, especially when you have no teammates. Well....maybe.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>58</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-05-12 22:24:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-05-12 22:24:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>sterling-road-race-reports</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/05/sterling-road-race-reports.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/1619885399735681003]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Blue Hills Classic</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=59</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2013 19:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=59</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<br><div><span><b><i>Andy Rothstein – Cat 4</i></b></span></div>
<div><span><br>In preparing for and thinking about the Blue Hills Classic I felt that coming over the top of Unquity when everyone was gassed from coming up the hill would be a good time to attack.  Apparently the eventual winner was thinking the same thing because I think that’s where he attacked after the first time up the hill.  When he was not too far in front I considered catching up to him.  But, I did not take any initiative and figured that since he was alone the group would catch him.  Others must have been thinking that too because no one went for him.  He was soon was out of sight.  And then out of mind.  There was no organized pursuit and we were racing for second place.   The second to last time up Unquity I began to think about positioning for the finish.  I wanted to be in the front 1/3 of the group so that I would not have to work too hard and when we went up Unquity again I would be positioned so as to not get caught behind struggling riders and so that my efforts would be expended at the front of the race and not trying to get to the front.  That plan worked well and I finished 3<sup>rd</sup> in the group…4<sup>th</sup> in the race (remember, there was a lone breakaway).<p></p></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div><span><b><i>Jonathan Doller – Cat 4</i></b></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div><span>The race started out innocently enough, but that would soon change.  I saw Andy Rothstein feign an early move to see who would respond, but no one did.  “I guess we’re going to ride 27 miles together and then settle this on the final climb,” I thought.  Boy, was I wrong!  Passing the ski slope for the first time, I took the opportunity to get out front and open the throttle a bit and stretch the legs.  On that fast section of the course, I knew I wasn’t really going to do any damage, but it sure felt good to ride with clear roads in front of me!  The first time up Unquity saw Sean Pantellere from STAMPEDE! attack over the top and would pretty much never be heard from again.  He got such a gap so fast that I think most of the field (myself included) didn’t even realize he was away (note to self: pay more attention).  Needless to say, the KOM on lap two was a formality as Pantellere was so far off the front that he was out of sight—not easy to do on the BHC course.  I’m pretty sure part of the reason we were never able to organize a chase is that most of the field didn’t realize that we were chasing!  The peloton stayed together for the remaining three laps with the pace quickening gradually as we approached the deciding climb up Unquity.  I was in good shape making the final right-hander and just tried to avoid riders slipping off the pace as both the speed and the incline increased.  I managed to do just that and got across the line in 7th place from the pack and 8th overall behind Pantellere.  With Rothstein grabbing a strong 4th, I’d say it was a good day for BHCC in our home race.<p></p></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div>
<b><i><span>B</span><span>art Lipinski – Masters 40+</span></i></b><span><p></p></span>
</div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div><span>Chilly cloudy morning, but luckily the sun poked out just in time for the start of the M40+’s.<p></p></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div><span>First lap a Wheelworks rider took off, but was reeled back in by the end of the first lap. On the 2<sup>nd</sup> lap, myself, a CCB rider and Expowheelman joined the Wheelworks rider and I was pretty sure we were going to get away. These were 3 strong riders and a good group to make something happen……well for at least a ½ a lap or so. It seem like the only time throughout the race the group showed any concern.<p></p></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div><span>A few more guys would peel off the front for a bit and a CCB rider almost made it without getting caught but it was coming down to a field group sprint. Ari was a great help in giving me just enough of a rest to get ready for the last climb up Unquity. <p></p></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div><span>I stayed about 10 wheels back and made sure to stay as far to the left as possible (as to not get boxed in). Just at the little flat before the last little climb to the finish I saw a rider out of the corner of my eye start to get out of the saddle…that was my queue to start my sprint.<p></p></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div><span>I went as far as I can to the left on the sprint, but the guy that initiated it was fading and trying to get out of the way. Of course he would swerve to the left. It kind of pinched me off just a bit, but don’t think it was enough to stop me from getting third. Was happy to take at least 6 spot on the sprint and not get passed. Definitely very pleased with taking 4<sup>th</sup>, but pissed I missed out on one of the sweet medals…..<p></p></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div><span>A couple of more tune ups (Duxbury TT and Sterling) before Killington. Feeling pretty good right now.<p></p></span></div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>59</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-05-06 19:33:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-05-06 19:33:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>blue-hills-classic</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/05/blue-hills-classic.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/1081652821320614478]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Quabbin Race Reports</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=60</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=60</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<span></span><br><div><span><span><b>Bart Lipinski - Masters 40+</b></span><span><p></p></span></span></div>
<span> <div><br></div>
<div>
<span>Awesome weather, first time I wore shorts without leg or knee warmers all season. Last year it was freezing and the year before….snow.</span><span><p></p></span>
</div>
<p></p> <div><br></div>
<div>
<span>First off, the race started off kind of hectic. 3.5 mile neutral start out of the park (all downhill), but when it did start, guys were going off the front like mad. Plus there was a good amount of climbing in the first hour as well. I wanted to stay with a few guys who I knew typically get in breaks, so I tried to stay with them or as close to the as possible.</span><span><p></p></span>
</div>
<p></p> <div><br></div>
<div>
<span>Here and there a guy or two would get up the road, but no one seemed concerned and we’d end up catching them. For the first hour it seemed like it was going to be a group ride to the end.</span><span><p></p></span>
</div>
<p></p> <div><br></div>
<div>
<span>At around 22 miles in, I knew there was a pretty good decent, so as we were cresting the top, I moved right out into the front (more because I wanted a clear view of the road for the descent). Worked hard to get some speed and took a peek back, and opened a gap of about 50 yards or so. At this point I was saying “oh shit….now what? It way too far out to try this alone, should I ease up?“ But then I heard someone say “Come on! Let’s keep this going!” Two guys crossed over and I was saying to myself “holy shit…..I just rode off the front!...and now have two others to work with!”</span><span><p></p></span>
</div>
<p></p> <div><br></div>
<div>
<span>For the next 10 miles we worked together really well, but I can still see the group, and they were not too far off. After the race I heard that we were left out to dangle for a bit.<span> </span> And it felt like it. Every time I took a peek over my shoulder I could still see the group.</span><span><p></p></span>
</div>
<p></p> <div><br></div>
<div>
<span>At around mile 35ish we had 3 more riders bridge over and that was a relief for me. I can honestly say that the 6 of us shared all the work; we all wanted to make this stick. At that point we were no longer seen by the field.</span><span><p></p></span>
</div>
<p></p> <div><br></div>
<div>
<span>Other than the miles not ticking away fast enough, I was feeling really good. I was working less in the break that I was the first hour trying to stay in contact with my marks. I was starting to feel it with about 7 miles to go. There were two climbs just outside the park that I felt like I could lose the group or my legs were ready to go (kinda like at Battenkill, felt like my thighs were going to cramp just over my knees). But managed to hang in there with them as we entered the park for the final 3.5 mile climb to the finish.</span><span><p></p></span>
</div>
<p></p> <div><br></div>
<div>
<span>We were still working great together although paranoid at this point that we were going to get caught. The last kick came at 200m, the pace picked up, I can see the finish line tent, but at this point didn’t have much of a sprint as the 4 in front of me pulled away. I was more than happy to finish 5<sup>th</sup>, to initiate the break that stuck for 43 miles, but wish I saved something somewhere in the race to have one last spurt. But hey, these are still practice races for Killington.</span><span><p></p></span>
</div>
<p></p> <div>
<span><br><br><b>Jonathan Doller - Cat 4/5 40+</b></span><span><p></p></span>
</div>
<div><br></div>
<div>
<span>Like all April races in the northeast, the weather for Quabbin can be as unpredictable as any out there.  As recently as 2011, race day saw about an inch of the slushy white stuff on the ground just to remind you that, regardless of what the calendar says, anything’s possible.  On a 65-mile route with just under 5,000 feet of climbing, the last thing you want to be fighting is the weather.  But, thankfully, Saturday dawned clear and cool with temps expected to rise into the mid-60s with just a hint of wind…in other words, perfect cycling weather.</span><span><p></p></span>
</div>
<p></p> <div><br></div>
<div>
<span>In the Cat 4/5 40+ field, one thing became clear very quickly: the experience/skill-level varied widely.  That gave me a bit of concern because one rider who gets a little twitchy on a descent can do a lot of damage to the field.  In fact, the carnage from some of the fields starting before us was apparent as we rode by either ambulances stopped on the side of the road or riders sitting in the grass waiting for assistance.  (On a side note, Quabbin’s also one of those races where you see a ton of guys early on riding in the opposite direction and you’re never sure if they’re just out for a weekend spin or if they’ve abandoned and decided to turn around and head back to the parking lot.)</span><span><p></p></span>
</div>
<p></p> <div><br></div>
<div>
<span> The course profile is one of those that looks like an EKG monitor readout (appropriate analogy considering the elevated heart rates pedaling up some of those climbs).  There are literally no flat sections.  Having raced Quabbin twice before and gotten popped off the back early each time, my goal was to just stay with the leaders over as many climbs as I could and, hopefully, onto the finishing ramp.  On the neutral start down the road from the parking lot to the park entrance, everyone was pretty much keeping to themselves with the occasional smell of hot brake pads wafting through the peloton.  Once out onto Route 9, a couple of guys tried to take some early fliers off the front, but only managed to get about a 30 second gap.  I did find myself at the front of the peloton a few times setting the pace, but no one was really pedaling in anger at this point and I didn’t feel like I was wasting any energy.</span><span><p></p></span>
</div>
<p></p> <div><br></div>
<div>
<span>Once the climbs started in earnest, the field was quickly slashed by about half.  I did well to stay close to the front on all the early climbs and descents.  The legs really started to burn around the 50-mile mark, but I did retain contact to what was still a pretty large lead group.  Passing the ball fields in Ware and back onto Route 9, I knew there were only 3 more climbs to get over, including the finishing climb.  I held on for the first 2 and most of the finishing climb back inside the park, but couldn’t match the accelerations at the final kick at 200m to go.  I managed to spin over the line shortly after the winner at 35<sup>th</sup>/78 place.  Finished in 3:00:40 (awarded same time as winner, but there were definitely some small gaps) at an average of 21.2 mph…considering my last Quabbin was a 3 hour, 44 minute “off-the-back” effort, I felt pretty good with the result.</span><span><p></p></span>
</div>
<p></p> <div><br></div>
<div>
<span><b>Andy Rothstein - Cat 4/5 40+</b></span><span><p></p></span>
</div>
<div><br></div>
<div>
<span>It was a beautiful day and I felt great. I stayed out of trouble for 63 some odd miles, ate right, and just rode with the group (there were no breakaways).  Near the end of the race we turned into the park for the climb to the finish and I was ready.  At one point I shifted into my inner ring because I wanted to spin more.  That's when my chain came off, notwithstanding my chain catcher.  I could not shift the chain back on and I had to stop and put it back on with my hand.  I watched the race ahead of me as I tried to not be left too far behind.  It was very disappointing (and my hand was a greasy mess)!  The silver lining is that I collected the best 5 minute power number I've ever recorded...and that came at the end of the race.  Looking forward to the Blue Hills Classic and another chance for success.</span><span><p></p></span>
</div>
<span><p></p></span></span>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>60</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-04-29 17:10:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-04-29 17:10:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>quabbin-race-reports</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/04/quabbin-race-reports.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/2760824388725165359]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Battenkill &amp; Myles Standish Race Reports</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=61</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=61</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><div><div><div>
<br><div><span><span><b><i><u>Jonathan Doller - Tour of the Battenkill, Cat 4A Race</u></i></b><p></p></span></span></div>
<div><br></div>
<div><span><span>Having raced Battenkill in 2010 and 2011 in the Cat 5s and gotten dropped on the first big climb each time, my goal for this year as a Cat 4 was pretty simple: hang on and hope for the best.  Race day dawned cool and damp, but since that’s pretty much how the entire Spring has been around here, it felt like any other day.  The only question was going to be what the conditions of the dirt sections were going to be with a dusting of snow hitting the area<span> </span><span>on Friday</span>.  They can be tough on a good day, but throw in some mud and puddles and anything can happen.<p></p></span></span></div>
<div><br></div>
<div><span><span>As we queued up for the 10:20 start, it was a bit foreboding as a pair of ambulances sped past and up the road.  One of the marshals looks over to our group and says, “Welcome to Battenkill.”  Thanks, buddy..!<p></p></span></span></div>
<div><br></div>
<div><span><span>The first 7 miles went as expected—riders jockeying for position along the stretch down Rt. 313 to try and be in good position for the acceleration through the covered bridge.  I was in good shape at about 15<sup>th</sup><span> </span>wheel and made it through without incident.  Soon after, the first climbs started with a steep paved ramp up Perry Hill Rd followed almost immediately by the ridiculously steep dirt ascent up Juniper Swamp Hill.  I was able to get up these climbs with the lead pack thus accomplishing my goal for the day!  Anything else was going to be icing on the cake.<p></p></span></span></div>
<div><br></div>
<div><span><span>The good feelings were short-lived, however, as all hell broke loose on the screaming descent down Rt. 64 into Salem.  Hitting the tough S-turn at the bottom, I saw trouble ahead as a rider at about 5<sup>th</sup><span> </span>wheel overcooked the turn, locked up his rear wheel and laid it down going about 40mph.  Chaos ensued as at least 10 riders plowed into the wreck.  At one point I saw someone’s Cervelo launched end-over-end about 15 feet in the air.  I had to steer into the dirt section on the left and put a foot down, but managed to squeeze through unscathed.  (Side note, there was an eerie silence in the peloton when, about 10 minutes later, another pair of ambulances—lights/sirens going—passed us from behind.  I hope those guys are OK.)<p></p></span></span></div>
<div><br></div>
<div><span><span>The group of 83 starters was whittled down to a pretty large lead group of about 30 or so riders over the climbs, descents, and sticky dirt sections of the next 40 miles.  I was still feeling strong both on the climbs and on the flats and started to have thoughts of a high finish for the first time.<p></p></span></span></div>
<div><br></div>
<div><span><span>We hit the final climb of Stage Rd and the lead group shattered.   1.4-miles long at about 5.5% and topping out only 5 miles from the finish, it’s where the race was going to be decided.  The lead group got pretty strung out on this climb, but reformed into two groups over the top.  I made the second group and saw the first group only about 500 meters up the road.  The chase was on!  My group started out working pretty well together and we started to claw back the leaders as the final kilometers ticked by.  But, with a combination of guys’ legs hurting and some riders with teammates up the road, we never made the final catch.  We made the final turn onto the finishing straight as a group of 10 riders as the second group on the road.  I did manage to take the sprint from the second group for a 12<sup>th</sup><span> </span>place overall finish at 36 seconds behind the winner.  Needless to say, I’m pretty happy!<p></p></span></span></div>
<div><br></div>
<div><span><b><i><u>Ted Myles - Cat 5H -<span> <span></span><span>Saturday, 12:50 pm</span></span></u></i></b><p></p></span></div>
<div><br></div>
<div><span><span>My first Battenkill, and aside from a couple of laps at Wompi, my first race!  Yikes, what a way to start!  I went into this thing not knowing what to expect. Was I going to win, or get dropped 300 meters into the race?  Anyone care to hazard a guess?  It wasn't quite 300 meters, I did hang with the group for about an hour.  I hammered up those insane climbs and felt strong enough to hang with the bulk of the peloton.  Ultimately however, it was lack of testicular fortitude, not lack of VOMax that did me in, although the latter probably would have caught up with me eventually!   I was absolutely amazed at how fast those guys took the descents!!!  I crested the first couple of hills with the lead group and then got blown away as they flew down dirt/mud/bumpy trails without a care in the world.  Eventually being a giant wuss and actually using my brakes on the descents and trying to catch up on the flats and the next hill sort of blew me up.  Once the bulk of the peloton disappeared I was oddly relieved to just enjoy hammering as much as I could, and to survive along the way!  With about 5k to go, got passed by someone from a group that started 10 minutes after me.  This pissed me off and I made it my mission to reel him in.  The last 500 meters I hammered away and beat him in a sprint finish by half a wheel.  It felt pretty awesome and gave me enough of a taste for racing to be pumped for Quabbin.  After crossing the line I congratulated the guy that passed me for beating me by 10 minutes, less half a wheel.  He laughed and we wished each other a great rest of the season.  Then I got some of that awesome Battenkill chocolate milk and watched some of the other finishes.  <p></p></span></span></div>
<div><br></div>
<div><span><span>Overall, it was an incredible day and I am really glad I did it.  I am looking forward to the fully paved roads of Quabbin and more racing and riding with BHCC!<p></p></span></span></div>
<div><br></div>
<div><span><b><i><u>Bart Lipinski – Tour of the Battenkill,<span>  </span>Masters 40+</u></i></b><p></p></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div><span>The weather was a little bit different on Sunday than Saturday. Unexpected rain Saturday night and a constant 15 mph wind from the west made for a pretty chilly start. <p></p></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div><span>The race stayed as a group up until about mile 17. 3 guys got off the front and since it was early and a long way to go, no one seemed concerned. The lead group stayed together right up to the final sprint (down to 29 guys at that point). I screwed up my positioning with about 1K to go. I wanted to stay on the outside to carry as much speed as possible through the last turn for the sprint, but was sucked up and stuck in the middle with little room to move forward until enough room opened up. I did make up about 5 or 6 spots in the last 200m, but not enough track left to get the other 11 guys. Missed 5<sup>th</sup> place by less than 1 second, ended up 15<sup>th</sup> overall.<p></p></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div><span>My strategy did not work at all throughout the race. I am somewhat convinced that I am now a marked man. No one in the group wanted to work. More than a few times one or two guys would get out to a 20 or 30 second lead over the group, but no one did anything. Only when I went to cross over, did the group follow. So, I ended up doing way too much work throughout the day. Probably bridged the gap about 5 to 6 times only to turn around and see the whole group right there with me. <p></p></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div>
<span><span><span>As for the rest, I felt great, especially climbing (I did fall back about 50 yards from the group on the last climb, but knew if I didn't get back on for the last decent, that I would be on my own for the ride into town. So I caught them). I didn't crash and nothing was broken. Off to the next one in the prep for Killington.</span></span><p></p></span><br><span><span><span><br></span></span></span><span><span><span></span></span></span><br><div><span><span><span><span><b><i><u>Doug Shepard - Battenkill 50+</u></i></b><p></p></span></span></span></span></div>
<div><span><span><span><span><br></span></span></span></span></div>
<span><span><span> <div><span>Stayed with the main group until about 38 minutes into the race, then slipped off the back, worked hard to get back on and rejoined right before one of the significant climbs. Turned out to be unfortunate timing, had burnt a match, then had to burn more.  Stayed with the pack over the top then was dropped for good.  The familiar getting dropped confusion, they were here a minute ago, where did they all go?  Kept a steady pace hoping to join some other stragglers, then the wheel truck passed, I hate it when that happens! Oh, well, I thought lets see what I can salvage.  Caught some stragglers, but they were cooked, they couldn't stay on my wheel, that was good moral boost but bad as I would not have any help.  Saw 2 riders several minutes ahead and worked for what seemed like 20 minutes to reel them in. One of them turned out to be my brother, I was really glad to catch up with him!, we traded pulls for the rest of the race, caught more stragglers and dropped them, got passed by the juniors who started 10 minutes behind us with about 25k to go, not bad holding the kids off for that long.  No one else from the 50+ group passed us.  Ended up in 50<sup>th</sup> place, out of 78 starters.<p></p></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div><span><b><i><u>Steven Fish – Battenkill Cat 5D<p></p></u></i></b></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div><span>I'll own up to having raced Battenkill last week as well.  Raced is a bit of misnomer, since I haven't raced in over 25 years, and this was a helluva way to relive my former "glory."  I rode it, cat 5D, and finished.  Not really much more to say about it other than the countryside was beautiful, my legs were heavy and dead from the get-go, and I spent a lot of time alone...just me, my bike, and my thoughts.  Maybe not the best choice to re-launch my racing career, but it gave me something to train for...and I beat a few guys 20 years my junior, for what that's worth.  Maybe next time I'll sign up more age appropriately (rode with friends in the 35+ category, big mistake).  Kudos to you, Myles, and Dorr for making a real race of it!<span><p></p></span></span></div></span></span></span><br><span><span><span><br></span></span></span>
</div>
<div><span><span><span><br></span></span></span></div>
<div><span><b><i><u>Ari Shocket – Myles Standish Road Race, Masters 35+</u></i></b><p></p></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div><span><span>While the true strongmen of BHCC were off competing in Battenkill last weekend, a number of us lesser humans were racing locally at the Myles Standish Road Race, sponsored by International Cycling.  Myles Standish is a neat little course that twists and turns through the Myles Standish State Park in Plymouth. I was racing in the masters 35+ field, which was stocked with many of the usual ex pros of the area.  Sam Morse from Corner Cycle got things started with an attack directly out of the parking lot and that set the tone for the next 2 or 3 laps.  Eventually, Mark McCormack got free with Bill Shattuck and Bill Yabroudy and a few others.  These breakaway specialists were never to be seen again and left the rest of us on a Sunday spin for 7th place at best.  I managed to get a small gap with 4 others on the final lap and rolled in at 10th.  Not bad for my first race of the season... Plus, it's always a success to finish that race without taking a swim in a pond!<p></p></span></span></div>
<div><br></div>
<div><span><span>I believe there were also some good results from Michael Roman, Jeff Lydon and Andrew Rothstein.  <p></p></span></span></div>
<div><br></div>
<div><span><b><i><u>Andy Rothstein – Myles Standish Road Race, Cat. 4</u></i></b><p></p></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div><span>I successfully navigated through the parts of the course with rough road and paid attention to positioning. At one time a rider got a 10 or 15 second lead on the group and since I had been sitting in I decided to catch up to him and see if we could get away. I made it up to him and we were alone, but the group did not like that so we were soon caught. At that time a counter attack happened and 2 or 3 others got off the front. I did not see that happen until it was too late and I did not try to catch them on my own thinking that the group would catch them.  That did not happen.  So I then focused on positioning myself for the finish. A big guy attacked and I went with him. He faded as a group caught us.  I stayed with them until the finish and ended up taking 8th place.  There is obviously a delicate balance of when to attack (or go with an attack) versus when to wait for an opportunity to counter attack (or go with a counter attack). </span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<div><span></span></div>
<div><span><b><i><u>Thomas Curtin - Myles Standish Road Race,  Cat 5 35+</u></i></b><p></p></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>
<span> </span><br><div><span>The first lap was pretty tame and I just sat in the back.  About two miles into the course was a rough section that I will refer to as the pave' (lots of potholes and bumps in the road).   The second lap saw an attempt at a break over the pave'.  They were reeled in pretty quickly,  Everyone took the third lap at a pretty leisurely pace in anticipation of the final lap.  I got to the front for the final lap prior to the pave'.  A group got away and I managed to jump on.  I got dropped over the next section, but managed to catch back on.  The lead group was about 12 - 15 strong.  I was on the rivet at this point.  There was another surge prior to the downhill left turn leading to the sprint finish.  I lost contact at this point and finished solo about 5-10 seconds down but was well ahead of the peloton.  Overall, I was pretty happy with how things went.  This was the first time racing this year- haven't been able to get any training races in.  A little more training/racing fitness would have put me in position for the sprint finish.<span><p></p></span></span></div>
<span></span>
</div></div></div></div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>61</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-04-17 16:02:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-04-17 16:02:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>battenkill-myles-standish-race-reports</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/04/battenkill-myles-standish-race-reports.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/5926561408022910455]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Michael Schott Race Reports - Rothstein &amp; Lipinski</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=62</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2013 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=62</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div>
<div>Early Sunday morning things were shaping up to be a fast day in <span>Marblehead</span> at the Michael <span>Schott</span> Memorial Circuit Race. Sun was shining, but that always blowing wind seemed to go through just about whatever you were wearing.</div>
<div><br></div>  <div><b>Andy <span>Rothstein</span> race in the 4/5's;</b></div>
<div><br></div>  <div><span>I raced at <span>Marblehead</span> Cat 4/5.  I was well positioned in about the front 20 for all but the first lap of the race.  On the last lap I got crowded out lining up for the final corner and lost position.  By the time I came up the final climb I had made up ground, but it was too late to catch back on to the front.  I ended up placing 17<span>th</span> about a few seconds off the winner.  I wish I could have applied my final effort at the front of the group instead of using it to make up lost ground.<p></p></span></div>
<div><span><br></span></div>  <div><b>Bart Lipinski – P123</b></div>
<div><br></div>  <div>I have to say, I was a bit nervous about this one, but <span>didn</span>'t feel the pressure I normally put on myself. I have been racing the P123's as practice races for better preparation in the master 40+ races. So, I decided to do something I normally do not do. I sat in.</div>
<div><br></div>  <div>The only work I was going to do was to keep myself where I felt I needed to be at certain point throughout the race. I had marked a few guys that I kept my eye on the entire race.</div>
<div><br></div>  <div>Throughout the whole race guys were going off the front. If it were a <span>CCB</span> guy, then there was a wall of teammates to get around. There were a few breaks that go off to about a 30-40 second lead, but all were reeled back in.</div>
<div><br></div>  <div>One big crash occurred sprinting out of the hairpin. It appeared that a couple of guys got tangled up. As we went around them, I had to dodge a real wheel that was bouncing down the road in front of me (was almost going as fast as me as well). </div>
<div><br></div>  <div>Big Dean from <span>Fitwerx</span> was marked by everyone. He did manager to break off the front with another guy with 2 laps to go. But surprisingly (at least by me) is that we caught him and he was swallowed up on the last turn.</div>
<div><br></div>  <div>I had a pretty good last lap. Was probably a little further back than where I wanted to be on the last turn, but did make up a bunch of positions coming out of the turn and up the last hill…..until I was almost taken out by the rider swerving in front of me. Plenty of time to react, but lost some of my momentum which probably cost me the chance to make a few more spot than I did.</div>
<div><br></div>  <div>In the end I finished 23<sup>rd</sup> out of 82 starters, just 3 seconds back from the winner.</div>
</div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>62</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-04-08 16:42:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-04-08 16:42:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>michael-schott-race-reports-rothstein-lipinski</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/04/michael-schott-race-reports-rothstein.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/3782137736141936623]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Andrew Rothstein - Charge Pond Race Report</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=63</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 13:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=63</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div>
<div><br></div>
<div>
<div> <div>
<div dir="ltr">Last Saturday, Charge Pond B Race.  Jon Doller and a dude from another team got away a little in the very early laps.  I and that other dude's teammate found ourselves on the front with no motivation to chase Jon and his companion and the rest of the group just followed us.  Once the group realized what was going on Jon and his companion, who were obviously working well together, had a nice gap.  I stayed on the front of the field for the rest of the race and followed just about every attempt that was made to bring Jon back and passively let the other pursuers do the work thinking that I could "counter attack" if we reached Jon.  I followed a lot of unsuccessful attempts and Jon stayed away with the other dude until the end of the race.  Jon took second to his breakaway partner, I took 6th from the field sprint, and Chad was 10th.  Three BHCCers finished in the top 10.     It was a training race, but I think we employed some nice tactics.  <br>
</div>
<div>
<br><br>
</div>
</div> </div> </div>  </div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>63</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-04-04 13:57:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-04-04 13:57:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>andrew-rothstein-charge-pond-race-report</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/04/andrew-rothstein-charge-pond-race-report.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/7465991292459030570]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Doug Shepard - Ninrgret 55+ Race Report</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=64</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=64</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><div><span><div>Bart:</div>
<div>just sending a report for the ninegret crit, Saw your race, but could not pick you out from the pack.</div>
<div>put me on the cat 3 race team (I gotta be the weakest cat 3 in history), or if you decide to make a masters group</div>
<div></div>
<div>Anyway, 1st race of the season was the ninegret crit 55+. Was good to have Brian Murphy as a teammate, we agreed to help each other out if the occasion arose.</div>
<div>Started with a bit of trepidation as the last fast ride in the pack was the jamestown race, nearly 6 months ago. my objectives were not to get dropped as Im frequently a weak crit rider. Found it much easier than expected to simply sit in. A 5 man break went off about 1/3 into th race, and the pace was   slowed by the blocking being done by the teammates of those in the breakaway. Once the breakaway had gotten out of sight, the pace picked up again. The wind picked up a lot on the back stretch, as it frequently does on this course. Got near the front a few times, but the usual churning of the pack made that temporary. Lots and lots of swerving of the leaders to make the chasers fight the wind. Saw the 10 lap to go sign, I thought if Im going to do something, its almost time to act. Couldn't believe I was even able to contemplate this, way cool if you've ever been forced to cook yourself simply to hang on.</div>
<div>I had kept an eye on Brian as he had flatted and had just rejoined the pack. There were a few attacks from those others who had some snap left, I waited for a promising wheel to follow. I jumped into a group of 3 and Brian latched on with 3 laps to go. We were in the lead of the chase group and turned into the wind, the front rider did   not pull through for some reason, so we were doomed as he would surely tire and we'd get caught. With 1 lap to go the pack caught us and the real attacks started, I was too close to the front and have no sprint to speak of so couldn't manage an effective response. Then the goal became don't be last, that was achievable ended up 25th out of 30 starters. Not bad for my 100th bike race, in fact Id consider it a success.</div>
<div>Doug</div></span></div></div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>64</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-04-04 13:55:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-04-04 13:55:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>doug-shepard-ninrgret-55-race-report</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/04/doug-shepard-ninrgret-55-race-report.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/528991193532871657]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Bart Lipinski - Chris Hinds P123 Race Report</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=65</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=65</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<br><div>3/30-3/31 BHCC Race Report</div>
<div><br></div>
<div>Racing in on for 2013!</div>
<div><br></div>
<div>Blue Hill had racers in both in Plymouth, Ma andCharlestown, RI this past weekend.</div>
<div>Jonathan Doller was able to get in a break on the first lapof the B race at Charge Pond. The group made it stick to the end and Jonathantook 2<sup>nd</sup> place!</div>
<div><br></div>
<div>Murph and I were down in Rhode Island at the Chris HindsMemorial Crit. It’s a crit course on some old runways along the water, so thereis always wind at this one. Murph took 12<sup>th</sup> place in the 50+ despitehaving to hit the pits to swap out a flat.</div>
<div><br></div>
<div>I raced in the P123’s and it was nothing but fast. I averaged 26 mph for the race, stuck with the lead pack and finished 22<sup>nd</sup> on the day. The entire field was lapped by two that got off the front early…not use to seeing the leader go flying by as your trying to set up for the final sprint, but was a great ride in prep for Marblehead next week.<br><br>A couple of pictures by my 11 year old head mechanic / coach, Jaymz<br><br><div><a href="http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-O9rceYFPicI/UVxlDsyuGaI/AAAAAAAAAAU/2SVmfyJNyi8/s1600/IMG_0373.jpg" imageanchor="1"><img border="0" src="http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-O9rceYFPicI/UVxlDsyuGaI/AAAAAAAAAAU/2SVmfyJNyi8/s1600/IMG_0373.jpg" height="240" width="320"></a></div>
<br><div><a href="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-eqOWS5TWihU/UVxlJHSdNvI/AAAAAAAAAAc/9UNlKUu3Qh4/s1600/IMG_0375.jpg" imageanchor="1"><img border="0" src="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-eqOWS5TWihU/UVxlJHSdNvI/AAAAAAAAAAc/9UNlKUu3Qh4/s1600/IMG_0375.jpg" height="240" width="320"></a></div>
<br><br>
</div>
<div><br></div>
<div><div><br></div></div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>65</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-04-03 17:22:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-04-03 17:22:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>bart-lipinski-chris-hinds-p123-race-report</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/04/bart-lipinski-chris-hinds-p123-race.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/3231916560215297535]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>2013 Blue Hills Classic Registration Open Tonight</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=66</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 18:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pete]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=66</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[2013 Blue Hills Classic - May 5th, 2013<br><br>Registration for the BHC opens tonight at 7pm.<br><br>To register click <a href="https://www.bikereg.com/Net/17962" target="_blank">here</a><br><br>The Cat 5 and 4 fields will fill up fast and I recommend signing up early. This event is also pre-reg only with no day of registration.<br><br>This year we added a new aspect to the race with a King of the Mountains competition. For the Cat 4 and 5 fields, the first across the line on lap number two will win BarFly mounts. The Masters and Cat 3s have two chances to win with KOM on laps 2 and 4. This may change some the dynamics of the race, but we will have to wait until race day to find out.<br><br>This race is very important for our club, and we will need as many volunteers as we can get to make it happen. We need course marshals, registration help, and drivers to lead and follow the pelotons. We will also need a few volunteers to help hand out notices to homes and businesses along the course a few weeks prior to the event, as well as a course sweep team the day before to mark road hazards and sweep any general road debris off the course.<br><br>Let me know what you would like to volunteer for.<br><br>Pete<br><br><br><br><br>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>66</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-03-15 18:08:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-03-15 18:08:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>2013-blue-hills-classic-registration-open-tonight</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/03/2013-blue-hills-classic-registration.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/4895390398145773763]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Clothing is in</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=67</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pete]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=67</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Our first run of Champion clothing has arrived. We will have a distribution night at Landry's in Norwood on Monday March 18th from 6-8pm. There will be plenty of refreshments to enjoy. Even if you didn't order clothing this round come down and meet some of the new members.<br><br>There is another order for clothing that is currently open to all members and will close on March 31st. If you need the login or help with the order reach out to Ari or Pete.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>67</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-03-14 21:37:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-03-14 21:37:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>clothing-is-in</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/03/clothing-is-in.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/5755013379206768701]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>BHCC Clothing Orders</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=68</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 22:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pete]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=68</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Just a quick reminder that BHCC clothing orders are due before the end of the month. All orders are handled online through Champ-Sys. If you need login information please contact Ari or Pete.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>68</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-01-26 22:07:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-01-26 22:07:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>bhcc-clothing-orders</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/01/bhcc-clothing-orders.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/1526236554580855047]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Off-Season Fitness Training</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=69</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=69</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div>
<p><span>Looking to up your game on the bike as well as improve your overall fitness?  Consider challenging yourself in 2013 by participating in the boot camp workout programs organized by fellow Blue Hills Cycling Club member, Maureen Conlon.  Perhaps, many of you have seen Maureen and her die hard boot campers running morning drills outside Fontbonne Academy or running up the Blue Hill access road.  Common weaknesses among cyclists are core strength and cardio endurance.  As you can see from the program descriptions below, there is a heavy emphasis on improving core strength and maximizing cardio-vascular performance in Maureen’s boot camp programs.  If you want to participate in a camp to get a sense of how far you can push yourself, you are welcome to show and go, much like the Club’s group rides.  For BHCC members wishing to participate in Maureen’s boot camp program, the drop-in rate is $12.00 per session.  If you prefer to preregister for the 4-week block of boot camps, the cost is $40.00 ($10.00 per class).  Feel free to contact Maureen directly at <a href="mailto:maureen@kneededtherapy.info"><span>maureen@kneededtherapy.info</span></a>.<p></p></span></p>
<p><span><p> </p></span></p>
<p><span>Murph<p></p></span></p>
<p><p> </p></p>
<p><b><span>ADVANCED BOOT CAMP<p></p></span></b></p>
<p><span> <p></p></span></p>
<p><span>* Meets Saturdays from 7-8:30am. Locations include Blue Hills; Fontbonne Academy (we meet here and cover all the hills and stairs in and around Adams St); Houghton's Pond; Milton Council on Aging (we meet here and cover hills and stairs by the hospital and neighboring streets).<p></p></span></p>
<p><span> <p></p></span></p>
<p><span>If you like to run, enjoy stairs and hills and are looking to strengthen your cardiovascular system, this is the class to take.  In 90 minutes, we run up and down all the hills and stairs Milton has to offer.  You'll be challenged with ankle bands, dogsleds, pushups (diagonal, negative, fast, slow) and lunges, to name a few. This class ends with an intense 15-20 minute abs and core workout.<p></p></span></p>
<p><span> <p></p></span></p>
<p><b><span>JUMP ROPE DRILLS<p></p></span></b></p>
<p><span>* Meets Friday mornings from 5:30-6:45am at the Fontbonne gym. Participants bring a jump rope and (1) 10 lb. weight for abs.<p></p></span></p>
<p><span> <p></p></span></p>
<p><span>The most intense class of the week is Jump Rope Drills.  In between our 5-minute jump rope sessions, we cover aerobic and anaerobic drills (sprints, crab walk, prisoner lunges, burpees, elephant walk, inchworms, jump lunges and power squats).  There's also a 5-7 minute ankle band drill that will leave your quads burning (in a good way)! This class ends with an intense abs and core workout that incudes using a 10 lb. weight for an added challenge.<p></p></span></p>
<p><span> <p></p></span></p>
<p><p> </p></p>
<p><p> </p></p>
<p><p> </p></p>
</div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>69</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2012-12-31 16:07:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2012-12-31 16:07:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>off-season-fitness-training</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2012/12/off-season-fitness-training.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/5805923543016389316]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Mini-Camp-Less Day 3</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=70</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 02:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=70</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><div><span>Tomorrow will also be a no go for any road rides. There might be an afternoon Wompy ride, so check on Facebook for any details. <br><br>We will also post any road rides on Facebook and on our calendar (<a href="http://www.bluehills.com/">www.bluehills.com</a>) that might occur on the warmer or dry weekend days. <br><br>Bart <br><br>Sent from my iPad</span></div></div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>70</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2012-12-31 02:43:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2012-12-31 02:43:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>mini-camp-less-day-3</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2012/12/mini-camp-less-day-3_30.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/3241513394386433462]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>New Site</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=71</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 00:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pete]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=71</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[New site is up and running. Take a look around. A guide for writing race reports, posting photos, and updating group rides will be sent to BHCC members soon.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>71</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2012-11-12 00:18:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2012-11-12 00:18:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>new-site</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2012/11/new-site.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/7164990031183083786]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>BHCC Race Reports</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=72</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 00:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=72</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Race Reports are a new feature to our website. Watch for reports this coming spring.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>72</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2012-11-12 00:16:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2012-11-12 00:16:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>bhcc-race-reports</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2012/11/bhcc-race-reports.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/3105941053313426489]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>NEW WEBSITE COMING SOON</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=73</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 04:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=73</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Our new website will be up and running soon. Stay tuned for a guide to all the new features.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>73</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2012-11-06 04:33:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2012-11-06 04:33:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>new-website-coming-soon</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2012/11/new-website-coming-soon.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/7612769093992901259]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Adams Farm Short Track Finale</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=619</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov -0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[BHCCAdmin]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=619</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Last night was the fourth and finale Adams Farm Short Track Training Race for 2014. The A Race Pace was Fast and Furious and those looking to get dizzy, see stars and maybe throw up were not disappointed. 



<a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/adams-farm-mtb-166_small.jpg"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-620" alt="adams-farm-mtb-166_small" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/adams-farm-mtb-166_small.jpg" width="500" height="263" /></a>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>619</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-08-21 13:35:19</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>0000-00-00 00:00:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name></wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>draft</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[4]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>New Kit Design</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=49</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pete]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=49</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><span><b>Introducing the new Blue Hills Cycling Club Kit for 2013/2014</b></span></div>

<div><br></div>

<div>



<a href="http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-27E6yTo767c/Uk7QQHkZT7I/AAAAAAAAAA8/oLHdHSNEdvg/s1600/20131004160820.Blue_Hills_Cycling_Club_US015765_JER001_Normal_v4_08.jpg" imageanchor="1"> <img border="0" height="280" src="http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-27E6yTo767c/Uk7QQHkZT7I/AAAAAAAAAA8/oLHdHSNEdvg/s1600/20131004160820.Blue_Hills_Cycling_Club_US015765_JER001_Normal_v4_08.jpg" width="320"></a></div>



<br><div><a href="http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-iPi37u6W-hc/Uk7QULidZpI/AAAAAAAAABE/F2zvhq0vhbw/s1600/20130925141543.Blue_Hills_Cycling_Club_US015765_BSH003_Normal_V4_07.jpg" imageanchor="1"> </a>



</div>

<div><br></div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>49</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-10-04 14:30:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-10-04 14:30:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>new-kit-design</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/10/new-kit-design.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/4057165609213152346]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Landmine Classic Mountain Bike Race</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=50</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 12:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pete]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=50</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<span>The Landmine Classic at Wompatuck is this Sunday. If you're new to MTB racing I recommend this one.<br><br>This race is great for so many reasons... it's close to us, its a fast and fun course that's mostly flat, typically has a great turnout, and offers many distances.<br><br>With the exception of the marathon class (50 miles) everyone starts at 10:30am.<br><br>I'll be there with a cooler of our sponsor's finest for after the race.<br><br>Registration is open on BikeReg https://www.bikereg.com/Net/18469</span>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>50</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-09-04 12:56:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-09-04 12:56:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>landmine-classic-mountain-bike-race</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/09/landmine-classic-mountain-bike-race.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/6751316915061206526]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Freetown 50 MTB Race</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=51</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 19:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pete]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=51</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[BHCC,<br><br>September seems to be marathon month. The weekend after the Landmine Classic, there is a new marathon race called The Freetown 50. All the important information is up on BikeReg and www.freetown50.com.<br><br>This race also has a 25 mile option and team relay options as well if 50 miles of mountain biking isn't your thing. The best part, it's very close.<br><br>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>51</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-08-28 19:04:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-08-28 19:04:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>freetown-50-mtb-race</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/08/freetown-50-mtb-race.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/4654283387661264559]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Mt. Washington Race Report</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=52</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 13:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=52</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<br><div><span><span><b><i>Trish Karter - Mt. Washington Race Report</i></b></span></span></div>

<div><span><span><br></span></span></div>

<div><span><span>Sorry for my late-arriving report.  Have been cruising in Maine. I’m happy to participate in the Ripper tradition of race reports as it was an excellent vehicle for processing everything. Thanks! </span></span></div>

<div><br></div>

<div><span><span>I intensified my training this year for what would be my 5th Mt. Washington Hillclimb and thus…. greatly intensified the <i>PRESSURE</i> to deliver! My terrific coach, Marti Shea (undefeated queen of BUMPS) put me up to it and gave me the road map to chase down a goal which would have been unthinkable for me just a few years ago. My wonderful (anonymous) sponsor made it possible to be on crazy good wheels but also to believe that I<i>should</i> ride them and <i>could</i> earn my keep on them. On Saturday morning it actually looked pretty promising. Equipment, training, weight, head game, logistics --- all race-ready. </span></span></div>

<div><br></div>

<!--more-->

<div><span><span>About 15 minutes before the Top Notch starting gun I was doing my first opener on the steep little hill behind Glen House which everyone likes to ride.  So it’s thick with people.  Everything was working well and I felt strong.  Then Bam! A 250 pound guy lost control of his bike and landed on top of me and I in turn landed on Carl.  Note to self:  don’t go there next year! I heard the hiss of air out of my new Zip 202 tubulars and saw the snapped-off valve on the pavement.  “Oh Shit!!” My adrenaline was pumping so hard I couldn’t really assess the bodily damage but the immediate question was whether I could get a wheel before the starting gun. There was some blood around but both Carl and I seemed fine and his bike was unscathed. Later that evening I found a whole new color scheme on my thighs and hip (the bad hip) but nothing, obviously, that kept me from riding. Hadn’t hit my head and it didn’t feel shaken. Never did get the color-scheme report from Carl but I know he was fine too – and tough! Actually I think I’ll rename the bad hip to “the good hip”.  It took the pounding.</span></span></div>

<div><br></div>

<div><span><span>Before that moment I had been observing the impressive range of humanity attempting this climb, appreciating the gorgeous bluebird day and feeling lucky to be there.  I hadn’t yet had that twisted-gut pre-gun moment of inner debate on why I do this, how much would it hurt and could I perform up to my expectations?  I always know the outcome of that debate but it seems to need to take place anyway. Answers to those questions deserve a whole separate exploration which I’ll spare you now. Summiting is a powerful experience every time, no matter what the circumstances or expectations. I think it must be the “summit high” that has reprogrammed my entire cell structure to crave the suffering which leads to it.  My first Mt. Washington was a celebration of being alive and having a brain that still works.  This climb was all that of course, plus a run at the notion, which I’d always held as a frustrated athlete, that I could “be someone”.</span></span></div>

<div><br></div>

<div><span><span>Up off the pavement and assessing the damage, I conjured a salve for the moment.  It was OK for one bad thing to have happened as it must be some kind of karmic trade toward one really good thing that might still happen. The big guy was a sweetheart – wish I had his name.  I told him not to worry and took off on a run – or rather a cleat-clump, down to the mechanic’s tent, carrying my crippled bike. My buddy Carl showed up with a replacement valve from another sweetheart who had observed the whole thing – wish I had his name too (I need to send him a valve).  Jeff the unflappable mechanic worked miracles and I made it to the starting line.  No doubt I was running my HR max for the day before the race had even started.</span></span></div>

<div><br></div>

<div><span><span>Carl by the way, who’s very fit from everything <u>but</u> cycling, was attempting this ride at the opposite end of the hill-climbing prep spectrum.  It worked out well for him in a not-too-fast kind of way.  Last year he led his legally blind cousin up the hill, stopping frequently to help the cousin deal with disorientation and nausea, then jumping back on his bike to continue the long slog. No doubt there are hundreds of stories like that on the mountain. My first year I met  someone (who has become a good friend) who was there with his four-brother support crew. He was celebrating his comeback from a stage four cancer.  </span></span></div>

<div><br></div>

<div><span><span>My own story was that I’d gotten into hill climbing as a way to stay fit and stay on a bike (even if it was an indoor trainer) without much risk of landing hard on my head….again.  In the Spring of 2010 I had a bike accident resulting in the usual collection of broken bones, dislocations and road rash. But it also left me with significantly impaired cognitive abilities from which it took about a year to fully recover. Actually some may argue they didn’t all come back and others say they prefer the slowed-down version of me.  </span>J<span> But I think my brain works better now after being rearranged. More importantly, I’m deeply grateful to have a brain!  Pre-race there had been debate about whether I should ride at all because of [yet another] concussion three weeks before which had sidelined me. That one was not a cycling accident and not my fault – just one of those things. But my doctor, whose “clearance to ride” I was going to get on Thursday, had to cancel the appointment. I decided that was a sign from the gods and promised my inner circle that I would scratch the race if at any point the head felt bad (unusual-bad as opposed to the regular Rockpile-intensity-bad). My head felt ready on Thursday. Honestly – and I did have to dig deep within to discern truth from desire.  And with that, I was hoping I could still perceive the distinction on Saturday while underway. No-one in the medical community seems to really understand the trade-offs – but the short term seemed fine. I do wonder about the long term - often and thoughtfully. I had scratched my last race at Equinox because of the head and that was clearly the correct choice. I believed I was making another correct choice regarding Mt. Washington.</span></span></div>

<div><br></div>

<div><span><span>I gave the ride pretty much what I had.  That turned out to be a LOT for the first couple miles – way faster than my plan – self-control issues.  Then for reasons I still don’t understand, I slowed down a lot in the middle (maybe burned a match?), especially when I hit the headwinds. Like Don, I have a strange affection for the dirt which is a welcome psychological break even though one stretch of it is particularly grueling.  That stretch is right after one of the few switchbacks and on this day the wind hit us like a brick wall right there. Still, there’s a “before the dirt” and an “after the dirt”. And it is <u>absolutely guaranteed</u> that you are a lot closer to the summit “after the dirt” -- I like that!</span></span></div>

<div><br></div>

<div><span><span>I realized around mile 5 or 6, painfully, very painfully, that I was going to miss the mountain record for women over 50 of 1:17 (my fondly held goal) set by Mary Hynes Johanson last year at age 57! Sadly she took a bad fall last week and broke her arm. I missed her presence on the mountain this year. It’s great to have a close competitor (she’s the one out in front).  Even better to have a competitor who’s a friend. Anyway, at the moment of disappointment I inexplicably managed to keep my head in the game and even cranked up the wattage at that point to turn in a not too shabby finish for the last couple miles. Some alternative energy source took over.  I hammered home with maybe a hair too much left in the tank.  It’s so hard to get it right but every year I get closer to the holy grail of spending 100% of my mental and physical resources optimally over the 7.6 miles.</span></span></div>

<div><br></div>

<div><span><span>Everyone reported it being a slow day but I’m still trying to figure that out.  The temperature was perfect. The air was clear and the sun was glorious. The headwinds were also tailwinds a lot of time.  Tailwinds are less helpful than headwinds are hurtful but by how much and how do they differ at various speeds and body types? These didn’t feel so ridiculously bad in comparison with the 60 mph steady gale that blew July 6<sup>th</sup> for Newton’s Revenge.  Were they 25 or 40 mph when they hit us on that spot on the mountain at that moment? Now that it’s all over does it matter? Yes. And by how much? Can’t say.</span></span></div>

<div><br></div>

<div><span><span>I stood up and cranked up the last bit of 20% grade with what I had left and expired over the finish line.  Once  breathing again, I was a little more distressed about missing my time goal by 3 minutes and missing top notch by seconds, than I was pleased to have taken 4 minutes off my PR.  Goals and dreams of glory aside, the finish line was reliably cathartic, gratifying and emotional.  In past years I’ve often had a support crew but not this day. I thought of myself as the support for Carl and Dave Raszman, one of my best buddies in my Milton cycling crowd who was making his maiden voyage, having ridden over many mountains in his younger days and solo across country. Impressive cyclist and great guy.  So I forgot to eat anything or take a recovery drink as I raced over to cheer them to the finish. I paid for that later in a major bonk back down at the tent and  awards ceremony.  But I held myself together long enough to fully enjoy the 1<sup>st</sup> place finish for my 55-60 age group. Even better, I learned that I was 5<sup>th</sup> overall for the women with my 1:20. And even better than that, the age and gender adjusted results put me in the #1 slot for the women and #17 for the guys. </span><i><span lang="EN"><a href="http://www.coolrunning.com/results/13/nh/Aug17_MountW_set6.shtml" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">http://www.coolrunning.com/results/13/nh/Aug17_MountW_set6.shtml</a></span></i><span lang="EN"> </span><span>  I like being the 17<sup>th</sup> guy but #1 is a better number I think – in the abstract. Only 4 women made the top 50 age/gender adjusted list (wonder what those algorithms are).   OK that’s the end of my very big and very immodest brag. <u>Please</u> forgive me for it. </span></span></div>

<div><br></div>

<div><span><span>Next year . . . I haven’t decided if there will be one. But I admit to already dreaming of crushing that record (Mary I know you’ll be crushing it as well). And I’m hoping that Marti will be back providing incomparable inspiration to cyclists of all stripe, but especially women of a certain age. Last year she was #1 woman and #2 age and gender adjusted rider/guy with a finish of 63 minutes. And I believe she can beat 63.  Definitely. Even now that she’ crossed over the 50 year mark. Marti defies all conventional wisdom about age and physical performance limitations – as do Don Metz, Ken Cestone, Gerry Clapper and others. Speaking of age, the youngest rider this year was a girl, 11 year old Maria Goodwin who finished in 2:07! Also the 14 year old daughter of 16<sup>th</sup> place finisher/great rider Eric Van denDries (sp?), Gabby, finished in an incomprehensibly fast 1:29.  <b>Go girls!!!</b>  Ah youth…and talent…and guts! Imagine that.  Gabby was only 9 minutes behind me. Keep an eye on her.  She shyly and modestly shrugs it all off as no big deal.  </span>J</span></div>

<div><br></div>

<div><span><span>Missing (and very much missed) this year were top racers and good friends, Dominique Codere and Christine Lameroux – both Top Notch riders and both among the most talented on the circuit.</span></span></div>

<div><br></div>

<div><span><span>Fellow BHCC’ers Adam Shutes and Steve Finch came in with great times of 1:09 and 1:18 respectively making for a really strong BHCC team finish – maybe inspiring a few more of you to join in next year?</span></span></div>

<div><br></div>

<div><span><span>The evening of the race I met up with good friends the Phinneys in Randolph for an old fashioned square dance.  It was a hoot and I felt light as a feather.  Wait… was that the dancing or the wine? I’ve been dry for race season.  Either way it was a great evening. Rippers Tom Keane (1:15) and Christine Wichers showed up for a few squares too. They and Rippers Ulandt and Pauline and I did a fabulous recovery ride the next morning. Ulandt and Pauline had given me a ride down the mountain and it was fun to hear from Ulandt what it was like to take an “easy practice ride” up Mt. Washington this year as he wasn’t in racing form.  Last year he finished in 1:06!</span></span></div>

<div><br></div>

<div><span><span>All around a great weekend.  Then I drove straight to Southwest Harbor, still in my cycling gear, and hopped on a boat that was literally waiting for me at the dock to depart for a week-long cruise back to Boston.</span></span></div>

<div><br></div>

<div><span><span>I look forward to seeing many of you for the 5 Notch ride in September – and how many of you next year on the Rockpile?</span></span></div>

<div><br></div>

<div><span>Best,</span></div>

<div><span><span><br>T</span></span></div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>52</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-08-26 13:21:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-08-26 13:21:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>mt-washington-race-report</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/08/mt-washington-race-report.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/5695660115428201147]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Landmine XC Course Recon Ride Aug 25th</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=53</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 16:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pete]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=53</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[BHCC,<br><br>We will have a Landmine course recon ride on Sunday Aug 25th. The ride will be a no drop ride on the full 25 mile course. If weather looks like it will not cooperate on the 25th we will ride the 24th. Meet at 8:30am in the main parking lot and plan for 2.5hrs of riding.<br><br>Pete]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>53</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-08-07 16:37:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-08-07 16:37:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>landmine-xc-course-recon-ride-aug-25th</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/08/landmine-xc-course-recon-ride-aug-25th.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/7659237976560893522]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>White Mountain Cycling Classic, Lincoln, NH</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=54</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/?p=54</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<br><div><span><b><i><span> </span>Jonathan Doller--Cat 4</i></b></span></div>

<div><span><span><span lang="EN">I know everyone talks about the importance of “recovery,” but I never knew first-hand how important it really is until this week. <span> </span>After completing the B2B last Saturday and then riding 4 times during the week averaging 40-45 miles each, my legs were pretty spent going into the weekend. <span> </span>By Friday, I was regretting riding so much.<span> <span> </span></span>My legs were heavy and the “burn” wasn’t going away as fast as usual. <span> </span>But, the White Mountain Cycling Classic is a really nice race (including a free T-shirt and free lunch after!) and I wasn’t going to miss it.</span></span><span><p></p></span></span></div>

<!--more-->

<div><span><span> </span>This race has a little bit of everything, which always makes for a challenging day in the saddle. <span> </span>It consists of 9-laps (which they shortened to 8 due to time, I believe) on a rolling circuit that has a couple of steep ramps, a couple of ripping descents, a few dicey corners and a long false-flat drag along the Kancamagus Highway. <span> </span>The constant accelerations and decelerations tend to make the peloton yo-yo quite a bit and, if you’re caught out, it can take a really big effort just to latch back on. Add to that the fact that the Cat 4 boys seemed a little tentative on the descents into the corners. <span> </span>I felt like I had to brake a lot more than I wanted to and wasted a lot of speed and momentum. <span> </span>Oh well, better to have a safe race than a fast one where guys end up on the tarmac.<span> </span> Luckily, having done this race last year, I sort of knew what to expect and managed to stay well-positioned throughout the race.</span></div>

<div><span><span> </span>The first lap, which is usually no more than a shake-down lap, was interesting, to say the least. <span> </span>We had something occur that I had never experienced. <span> </span>As we approached the start/finish at the end of the lap, the officials stopped the entire peloton and pulled us off the course! <span> </span>Apparently, there were reports of guys violating the yellow line rule on the Kanc. <span> </span>It must have been behind me, because I didn’t see anything from where I was. <span> </span>At any rate, the whole field basically got put in “time out” for a few minutes while the official gave us a scolding. <span> </span>We had to let the Cat 5 field (which started a few minutes after us) pass before we were released. <span> </span>So now, in addition to racing each other, we were also dodging the Cat 5 guys who had gotten dropped. <span> </span>The whole thing was a bit strange, to say the least.</span></div>

<div><span><span> </span>Once we got back to racing, the laps started ticking by with a couple of small attacks on the hills and a couple of little digs on the Kanc. <span> </span>Each time, however, the whole field was back together in a matter of minutes.<span> <span> </span></span>It was definitely looking like a group sprint finish. <span> </span>The last time up the climbs, I slipped off the lead group a bit, but was able to catch back on by the time we took the right-hander onto the Kanc for the final time. <span> </span>However, right when I needed a little recovery from my effort just to catch back on, someone up front decided it was time to put the hammer down! <span> </span>I struggled to hang on for a few minutes but finally got tailed off the back with about 4 other riders with about 2 miles to go. <span> </span>The lead group was tantalizingly close, maybe 200 meters up the road, but the group I was in didn’t have the legs to catch back on before the final turn into the Loon Mountain parking lot. <span> </span>Knowing we weren’t going to factor in the finish, I sat up a bit to ride to the finish. <span> </span>When the guys I was with started sprinting for the 16<sup>th</sup><span> </span>place finish (where were those legs when we were chasing, boys?!), I was content to just spin across for a 20<sup>th</sup><span> </span>place finish at 28 seconds behind the winner. </span></div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>54</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-06-24 16:54:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-06-24 16:54:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>white-mountain-cycling-classic-lincoln-nh</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_blog</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[bluehillscyclingnews.blogspot.com]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>blogger_permalink</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/2013/06/white-mountain-cycling-classic-lincoln.html]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_blogger_self</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://www.blogger.com/feeds/1057267819093776335/posts/default/5274659164588327000]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>2014 Membership Open!</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=126</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 17:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pete]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=126</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[2014 club membership is now open on <a href="https://www.bikereg.com/Net/blue-hills-cycling-club-membership" title="Bikereg." target="_blank">Bikereg</a>.



We are working on a some great new programs for the club and have added a racer incentive program. 



Also, a short track series is coming to Adams Farm. Click on "Our Races" for more info. ]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>126</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-12-01 17:38:47</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-12-01 17:38:47</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>2014-membership-open</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Want to get fast this offseason? Get a fitting</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=130</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 18:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pete]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=130</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Over the last few weeks I've received many emails asking how they can improve their riding this off season. Besides the obvious of proper training and nutrition, the next best thing is a professional fitting. I am still shocked at how many riders don't get fitted to their bike. I recently purchased a new frame and documented the fit process. Whether you've had a fitting before or not, you'll want to read this article.



<a href="http://holdfastcoaching.com/Articles_List/Entries/2013/12/1_Fittings.html" title="Hold Fast Coaching" target="_blank">http://holdfastcoaching.com/Articles_List/Entries/2013/12/1_Fittings.html</a>



Pete

]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>130</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2013-12-05 18:21:03</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2013-12-05 18:21:03</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>want-to-get-fast-this-offseason-get-a-fitting</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_amt_description</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[THis is my custom description]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>King of the Blue Hills</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=202</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 18:47:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=202</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<strong>Do you think you have what it takes to be King of the Blue Hills?</strong>



<table><tr><td style="width:155px">

<a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/king.jpg"><img src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/king-150x150.jpg" alt="king" width="150" height="150" class="alignnone size-thumbnail wp-image-182" /></a>

</td><td><p style="padding-left:3px">This year we will be tracking club member’s efforts on your favorite road and dirt segments in and around the Blue Hills in order to find out who is truly the King and/or Queen of the Blue Hills. We will be tracking the dirt climbs in a separate competition</p> 

<p>For this competition we will only be looking at efforts completed in 2014, more specifically March through October. </p>

 </td></tr>

</table>





<p style="padding-top:5px">

Each segment will be weighted based on difficulty and points will be awarded to each of the top ten times for each segment.  The person with the most points wins. We are still evaluating the segments, expect this to be locked in by March 1st.  For complete contest rules and eligibility click on the King of the Blue Hills tab above. The King of the Blue Hills competition is only open to current members of the blue hills cycling club.  To Join the fun, please Join the Blue Hills Cycling Club by clicking on the link below. New members are always welcome!</p>



       <div class = "row"style ="display: table; margin:0 auto; padding-bottom:20px" >

        <a href="https://www.bikereg.com/Net/21860" target="_blank"><img  src="BHCC-3/img/bikereg.gif" alt="Join"/></a>

        </div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>202</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-02-14 18:47:38</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-02-14 18:47:38</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>king-of-the-blue-hills-2</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>BHCC Race Training Ride</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=210</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 03:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=210</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<table >

 <tr style = "padding-bottom:10px;">

  <td style="width:85px"><a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/murph.jpg"><img src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/02/murph-150x150.jpg" alt="murph" width="80" height="80" class="alignnone size-thumbnail wp-image-225" /></a></td>



  <td style="padding-left:10px" >On March 15th, <a href="http://e3ts.com/" title="E3 Training Solutions" target="_blank">E3 Training Solutions</a> - Cycling Head Coach, Brian Murphy will be leading a race simulation ride for the Blue Hills Cycling Club. The ride is open to all Blue Hills Cycling Club Members but will be limited to the first 15 riders That step forward.</td>

</tr>



</table>



<p style = "padding-top:10px;">

<u ><strong >Format:</strong></u>



<ul>

	<li>Warmup -30 Min</li>

        <li>Race Block - 60 min controlled moderate pace interval (18mph – 20mph)</li>

        <li>Tempo Interval - 30 min (17mph – 19mph) 

        <li>Race Block - 60 min controlled moderate pace interval (18mph – 20mph)</li>

</li>





</ul>







<u><strong>Race Intervals per 60 min Race Block:</strong></u>

<ul>

	<li>2 - Intermediate Sprint Intervals. Sprint points will be awarded 4 deep: 6-4-3-1</li>

	<li>2 - KOM’s. KOM points will be awarded 3 deep: 5-3-1</li>

        <li>Breakaway (Interval 1 only) – Any rider or breakaway group that executes a clean break (> 30 sec gap) and stays away from the group during a preset 3 mile interval will be awarded race points. Solo break will be awarded 8 points. Group breaks will be awarded 10 points to be divided evenly among the riders in the group.	</li>

        <li>Rider with the most accumulated points wins the General Classification (GC)</li>

</ul>



For more information, join the discussion on the <a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/bluehillscyclingclub/">Blue Hills Cycling Club Face Book Page</a>. 



If you are not a member of the Blue Hills Cycling Club and are interested in events like this, you can join the club on <a href="https://www.bikereg.com/Net/21860">Bikereg</a>. New members are always Welcome!



</p>



]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>210</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-02-26 03:41:51</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-02-26 03:41:51</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>bhcc-race-training-ride</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>ProXCT / US Cup in Austin, TX</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=246</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 19:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pete]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=246</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[I've pretty much had it with this winter and I was looking for any excuse to ride in some warm weather. So, in a last minute decision, I decided to head down to Austin to start my season about 6 weeks early. The weather was just about perfect, high 70s and dry. I arrived Thursday afternoon and immediately got a few laps on the course. The course was super fast, with a few punchy climbs and a ton of loose rocky corners.



Friday was registration, number pick up, and call up assignment. I pulled 42 for call up which would put me around row 5. Pretty good spot considering I don't have any UCI points. Two other New England riders (Tom Sampson and Billy Melone) and I headed out to do a few laps and immediately I ran into issues.  About 8 minutes into the ride, I slashed a tire open so bad that nothing was going to stop the leak. "Better today than race day" I kept telling myself. Still dressed in my kit, I drove to the nearest shop and picked up a new tire, installed it, then hustled back to the course to finish course inspection.  It was only about 3pm by the time I got back, so there was no rush, but the stress of the situation was making me anxious. After a lap, I settled down and was able to put the mishap behind me.



Race day was great, media everwhere, tons of fans, and sunny skies. I shook the nerves, got a good warm up in, and heading to the start area for staging and call ups. It was about 82 degrees when the whistle blew, and we were off on the 1km start loop. About 200 yards into the  race, the course bottlenecked and went uphill. Immediately the back of the pack came to a stop. There just wasn't enough room and everyone was fighting for position. After everything cleared out, we were all back on our way and chasing to get back on. The next bottleneck came after the double track heading into the singletrack between two tight trees. So many guys were trying to squeeze through at the same time, it was complete chaos. We came to a standstill and it seemed like a minute before we got going again. Now it was time to start chasing. The field was pretty spread out at this point and I settled into a group of 3-4 riders. After a lap or two, there were riders dealing with mechanical problems left and right. I knew I had to focus on riding smart and make advancements when I could. It would be a race of attrition, and staying smooth and consistent would be better than going all out and breaking equipment.



Half way through the 4th lap, I was going around a sweeping turn and my rear brake gave out. I told myself it wasn't a big deal, it just means I can't go as hard on the downhills. With no rear brake, I started to get a little sloppy and had to slow down. Just before the final feed zone, about 1/4mile from the finish, the insanely fast lead group of 4 (Plaxton, Kabush, Wells, and Bishop) caught me. I let them pass with ease and knew that the race would be done when I reached the finish. I just needed to make sure I didn't let anyone else catch me, I wanted to make sure I got a result. When I rolled through the finish, it was for 51st. Not as good as I hoped, but it's still early.



There was media everywhere, once some photos surface, I'll add them to the post. I'm thinking I'll head to the Fontana ProXCT race later this month. Anyone else want to go?



Pete]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>246</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-03-02 19:44:12</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-03-02 19:44:12</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>proxct-us-cup-in-austin-tx</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[2]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Blue Hills Kicks of the 2014 Race Season</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=251</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 16:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=251</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[The racing season is in full swing and the BHCC road team was spread out across the Northeast in both upstate NY for the Tour of the Battenkill as well as Marblehead, MA for the Michael Schott Memorial Circuit Race. There were a lot of great results at both Check out the latest Reports in the <a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/forum/viewforum.php?f=35" title="Forum">Forum</a>!

<table class="datatable1" width="100%">

								<tr><td colspan="5" class="headerrow3"><h5>Michael Schott Memorial Memorial Circuit Race (Apr 6 2014)</h5></td></tr>

					

									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>Michael</a></td>

					<td>O'donnell</a></td>

					<td>Men C4 C5  </a></td>

					<td width="70px">6 / 74</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow1">

					<td>

					<td>

					<td>

					<td width="70px">

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>Andrew</a></td>

					<td>Rothstein</a></td>

					<td>Men C4 C5  </a></td>

					<td width="70px">16 / 74</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow1">

					<td>Nate</a></td>

					<td>Sievers</a></td>

					<td>Men C4 C5  </a></td>

					<td width="70px">30 / 74</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>Scott</a></td>

					<td>Harrington</a></td>

					<td>Men C4 C5  </a></td>

					<td width="70px">65 / 74</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow1">

					<td>

					<td>

					<td>

					<td width="70px">

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>

					<td>

					<td>

					<td width="70px">

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow1">

					<td>

					<td>

					<td>

					<td width="70px">

					</tr>

									<tr><td colspan="5" class="headerrow3"><h5>Tour of the Battenkill Gran Fondo (Apr 6 2014)</h5></td></tr>

					

									<tr class="datarow1">

					<td>John</a></td>

					<td>Bosley</a></td>

					<td>Men Gran Fondo Master 60-64</a></td>

					<td width="70px">6 / 9</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>Jeffrey</a></td>

					<td>Bradley</a></td>

					<td>Men Gran Fondo Master 55-59</a></td>

					<td width="70px">20 / 22</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow1">

					<td>Michael f.</a></td>

					<td>Connolly</a></td>

					<td>Men Gran Fondo Master 50-54</a></td>

					<td width="70px">27 / 33</a></td>

					</tr><tr>

                    <a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/batt.jpg"><img src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/batt.jpg" alt="batt" width="525" height="324" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-264" /></a></tr>

									<tr><td colspan="5" class="headerrow3"><h5>Tour of the Battenkill (Apr 5 2014)</td></h5></tr>

					

									<tr class="datarow1">

					<td>

					<td>

					<td>

					<td width="70px">

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>Adam</a></td>

					<td>Shutes</a></td>

					<td>Men Master  35+</a></td>

					<td width="70px">19 / 41</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow1">

					<td>Steven</a></td>

					<td>Fish</a></td>

					<td>Men Cat 5 J 45+</a></td>

					<td width="70px">31 / 43</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>Peter</a></td>

					<td>Werner</a></td>

					<td>Men Cat 5 D 35+</a></td>

					<td width="70px">7 / 53</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow1">

					<td>Chad</a></td>

					<td>Guevremont</a></td>

					<td>Men Cat 5 D 35+</a></td>

					<td width="70px">41 / 53</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>Scott</a></td>

					<td>Harrington</a></td>

					<td>Men Cat 5 A</a></td>

					<td width="70px">33 / 57</a></td>

					</tr>

                    									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>Patricia</a></td>

					<td>Brownell</a></td>

					<td>Women Cat 4 A</a></td>

					<td width="70px">18 / 34</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow1">

					<td>Nicholas</a></td>

					<td>Stefanidakis</a></td>

					<td>Men Cat 4 A 40+</a></td>

					<td width="70px">15 / 101</a></td>

					</tr>

                    <tr class="datarow2">

					<td>Scott</a></td>

					<td>Taylor</a></td>

					<td>Men Cat 4 A 40+</a></td>

					<td width="70px">7 / 101</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>Jonathan</a></td>

					<td>Doller</a></td>

					<td>Men Cat 4 A 40+</a></td>

					<td width="70px">17 / 101</a></td>

					</tr>

                    <tr class="datarow2">

					<td>Kevin</a></td>

					<td>Brandt</a></td>

					<td>Men Cat 4 A 40+</a></td>

					<td width="70px">19 / 101</a></td>

					</tr>

                    									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>John</a></td>

					<td>Fice</a></td>

					<td>Men Cat 4 A 40+</a></td>

					<td width="70px">42 / 101</a></td>

					</tr>

                    									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>Philip</a></td>

					<td>Golden</a></td>

					<td>Men Cat 4 A 40+</a></td>

					<td width="70px">17 / 101</a></td>

					</tr>



									<tr class="datarow1">

					<td>

					<td>

					<td>

					<td width="70px">

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>

					<td>

					<td>

					<td width="70px">

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow1">

					<td>Victor</a></td>

					<td>Milligan</a></td>

					<td>Men Cat 4 A 40+</a></td>

					<td width="70px">69 / 101</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>Mark</a></td>

					<td>Brownell</a></td>

					<td>Men Cat 4 A 40+</a></td>

					<td width="70px">71 / 101</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow1">

					<td>Edward</a></td>

					<td>Myles</a></td>

					<td>Men Cat 4 A 40+</a></td>

					<td width="70px">100 / 101</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>Torrance</a></td>

					<td>Kopfer</a></td>

					<td>Men Cat 3  </a></td>

					<td width="70px">97 / 119</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr><td colspan="5" class="headerrow3"><h5>12th Annual Chris Hinds Memorial Criterium (Mar 29 2014)</h5></td></tr>

					

									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>

					<td>

					<td>

					<td width="70px">

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow1">

					<td>

					<td>

					<td>

					<td width="70px">

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>

					<td>

					<td>

					<td width="70px">

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow1">

					<td>Brian</a></td>

					<td>Albert</a></td>

					<td>cat 5</a></td>

					<td width="70px">7 / 12</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>Andrew</a></td>

					<td>Rothstein</a></td>

					<td>cat 3-4</a></td>

					<td width="70px">19 / 41</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow1">

					<td>

					<td>

					<td>

					<td width="70px">

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>Nate</a></td>

					<td>Sievers</a></td>

					<td>cat 4</a></td>

					<td width="70px">3 / 28</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow1">

					<td>

					<td>

					<td>

					<td width="70px">

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow2">

					<td>

					<td>

					<td>

					<td width="70px">

					</tr>

									<tr class="datarow1">

					<td>Andrew</a></td>

					<td>Rothstein</a></td>

					<td>cat 4</a></td>

					<td width="70px">26 / 28</a></td>

					</tr>

									<tr><td colspan="5" class="headerrow3"><h5>Greenville Spring Series (Mar 1 2014)</h5></td></tr>

					

									<tr class="datarow1">

					<td>Andrew</a></td>

					<td>Rothstein</a></td>

					<td>Men Masters 40+  40+</a></td>

					<td width="70px">26 / 37</a></td>

					</tr>

</table>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>251</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-04-07 16:06:15</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-04-07 16:06:15</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>blue-hills-kicks-of-the-2014-race-season</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Cat 4 Team Survives Myles Standish, Mountain Bikers Hit the Root 66 Season Opener at Hopbrook Dam</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=284</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 10:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=284</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Two major crashes during the Myles Standish CAT 4 Race resulted in the dispatch of ambulances to tend to the wounded. A few BHCC racers got caught in the crash but fortunately none were wounded.

<a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/mylesstandish.jpg"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-278" alt="mylesstandish" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/mylesstandish.jpg" width="580" height="170" /></a>
<table class="datatable1" width="100%">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td class="headerrow3" colspan="5">
<h5>Myles Standish State Forest Road Race (Apr 13 2014)</h5>
</td>
</tr>
<tr class="datarow2">
<td>Ari</td>
<td>Shocket</td>
<td>Men MASTER 35+</td>
<td width="70px">17 / 38</td>
</tr>
<tr class="datarow1">
<td>Brian</td>
<td>Albert</td>
<td>Men C5</td>
<td width="70px">9 / 40</td>
</tr>
<tr class="datarow2">
<td>Scott</td>
<td>Harrington</td>
<td>Men C5</td>
<td width="70px">16 / 40</td>
</tr>
<tr class="datarow1">
<td>Michael</td>
<td>O'donnell</td>
<td>Men C4</td>
<td width="70px">13 / 45</td>
</tr>
<tr class="datarow2">
<td>Algis</td>
<td>Norkevicius</td>
<td>Men C4</td>
<td width="70px">16 / 45</td>
</tr>
<tr class="datarow1">
<td>Jonathan</td>
<td>Doller</td>
<td>Men C4</td>
<td width="70px">19 / 45</td>
</tr>
<tr class="datarow2">
<td>Nate</td>
<td>Sievers</td>
<td>Men C4</td>
<td width="70px">26 / 45</td>
</tr>
<tr class="datarow1">
<td>Adam</td>
<td>Shutes</td>
<td>Men C4</td>
<td width="70px">37 / 45</td>
</tr>
<tr class="datarow2">
<td>Kioko</td>
<td>Mwosa</td>
<td>Men C4</td>
<td width="70px">42 / 45</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
&nbsp;

<img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-290" style="line-height: 1.5" alt="hopbrook" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/hopbrook.jpg" width="579" height="446" />

&nbsp;

Three Riders headed down to Hop Brook Dam MTB Race for official launch of the Root 66 Race Series . You can check out their race reports in the <a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/forum/viewforum.php?f=37" target="_blank">forum</a>.
<table class="datatable1" width="100%">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td class="headerrow3" colspan="5">
<h5>Hop Brook Dam, Middlebury CT April 13th, 2014</h5>
</td>
</tr>
<tr class="datarow2">
<td>Pete</td>
<td>MacLeod</td>
<td>Pro Open</td>
<td width="70px">9/25</td>
</tr>
<tr class="datarow1">
<td>Philip</td>
<td>Golden</td>
<td>Men C2 40-<span style="font-size: 11px;line-height: 2">49</span></td>
<td width="70px">6/29</td>
</tr>
<tr class="datarow1">
<td>Richard</td>
<td>Walsh</td>
<td>Men C3 50+</td>
<td width="70px">3/3</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
&nbsp;]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>284</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-04-15 10:22:31</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-04-15 10:22:31</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>cat-4-team-survives-myles-standish-mountain-bikers-hit-the-root-66-season-opener-at-hopbrook-dam</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Another Boston Marathon Ride In The Books and Racing Continues!</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=301</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 00:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=301</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/bostonmarathon.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-312" alt="bostonmarathon" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/bostonmarathon.jpg" width="545" height="291" /></a>



&nbsp;



BHCC had another succesfull ride along the Boston Marathon Route this Marathon Monday. 6 Mountain Bikers hit the dirt at the 2nd stop of the Root 66 Race series while Johnathan Doller led the CAT 4 Team to a podium finish at the Mystic Velo Criterium. You can read about their race reports <a href="http://http://www.bluehillscycling.com/forum/">here in our forum</a>.

<table class="datatable1" width="100%">

<tbody>

<tr>

<td class="headerrow3" colspan="5">

<h5>Rocky Woods Lung Challenge, Taunton, MA April 19th, 2014</h5>

</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow2">

<td>Pete</td>

<td>MacLeod</td>

<td>Pro Open</td>

<td width="70px">999</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td>Pete</td>

<td>Werner</td>

<td>Men CAT 1 30-39</td>

<td width="70px">7/17</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td>Scott</td>

<td>Taylor</td>

<td>Men CAT 2 40-49</td>

<td width="70px">5/22</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td>Tucker</td>

<td>Walsh</td>

<td>Men CAT 2 40-49</td>

<td width="70px">8/22</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td>Ted</td>

<td>Myles</td>

<td>Men CAT 3 40-49</td>

<td width="70px">4/7</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td>Rick</td>

<td>Doherty</td>

<td>Men CAT 3 40+</td>

<td width="70px">7/7</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td>Richard</td>

<td>Walsh</td>

<td>Men CAT 3 50+</td>

<td width="70px">6/7</td>

</tr>



</tbody>

</table>

&nbsp;

<table class="datatable1" width="100%">

<tbody>

<tr>

<td class="headerrow3" colspan="5">

<h5>Mystic Velo Criterium, April 19th, 2014</h5>

</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow2">

<td>Jonathan</td>

<td>Doller</td>

<td>Men Cat 4 Open</td>

<td width="70px">3/36</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td>Michael</td>

<td>O'donnell</td>

<td>Men Cat 4 Open</td>

<td width="70px">8/36</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td>Austin</td>

<td>Guyette</td>

<td>Men Cat 5 Open</td>

<td width="70px">8/15</td>

</tr>

</tbody>

</table>

&nbsp;]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>301</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-04-23 00:32:57</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-04-23 00:32:57</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>annual-boston-marathon-ride-a-success-and-racing-continues</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>More Solid Results at the Quabbin Reservoir Classic</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=328</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=328</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[The Road Team was out in force at the Quabbin Reservoir Classic suffering through some brutal conditions. You can read their stories <a href="http://http://www.bluehillscycling.com/forum/">here in our forum</a>.



&nbsp;

<table class="datatable1" width="100%">

<tbody>

<tr>

<td class="headerrow3" colspan="5">

<h5>Quabbin Reservoir Classic Road Race (Apr 26 2014)</h5>

</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow2">

<td>Jonathan</td>

<td>Doller</td>

<td>4/5 40+</td>

<td width="70px">14/31</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow2">

<td>William</td>

<td>Paredes</td>

<td>4/5 40+</td>

<td width="70px">26/31</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td>Adam</td>

<td>Shutes</td>

<td>C 4/5</td>

<td width="70px">10/44</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td>Brian</td>

<td>Albert</td>

<td>C 4/5</td>

<td width="70px">31/44</td>

</tr>

</tbody>

</table>

&nbsp;

<table class="datatable1" width="100%">

<tbody>

<tr>

<td class="headerrow3" colspan="5">

<h5>ECCC Conference Championships Criterium (Apr 28 2014)</h5>

</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow2">

<td>Chad</td>

<td>Guevremont</td>

<td>C 4/5</td>

<td width="70px">32/46</td>

</tr>

</tbody>

</table>

&nbsp;



<a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/Rich.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-335" alt="Rich" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/Rich.jpg" width="545" height="388" /></a>

<table class="datatable1" width="100%">

<tbody>

<tr>

<td class="headerrow3" colspan="5">

<h5>Fat Tire Classic, Winding Trails, Farmington, CT (Apr 27 2014)</h5>

</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow2">

<td>Richard</td>

<td>Walsh</td>

<td>Cat 3 50 +</td>

<td width="70px">10/12</td>

</tr>

</tbody>

</table>

&nbsp;]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>328</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-05-05 10:11:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-05-05 10:11:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>more-solid-results-at-the-quabbin-reservoir-classic</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Mount Blue Criterium</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=340</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 20:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=340</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Despite having only a few weeks to pull together a venue change due to the unsafe road conditions, Pete Macleod was able to string together a really fun event with an awesome Boston's Baddest Burgers food truck, some super Flat Black coffee and lots of hard, fun racing.



<a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/mikecrit.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-341" alt="mikecrit" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/mikecrit.jpg" width="512" height="289" /></a>



&nbsp;



Thanks to all of the volunteers working registration, parking and course marshalling. Without you, we can't pull these events off.



<a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/volunteers1.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-345" alt="volunteers" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/volunteers1.jpg" width="545" height="261" /></a>



&nbsp;

<h5>Ari Shocket (Masters 40+) and Mike O’Donnell (Cat 4) on the Podium!</h5>

&nbsp;



<a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/ariandmike.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-349" alt="ariandmike" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/ariandmike.jpg" width="545" height="181" /></a>



<img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-351" alt="cat4 team" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/cat4-team.jpg" width="545" height="282" />

<table class="datatable1" width="100%">

<tbody>

<tr>

<td class="headerrow3" colspan="5">

<h5>Mount Blue Criterium (May 4 2014)</h5>

</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Chad</td>

<td>GUEVREMONT</td>

<td>Cat 5A</td>

<td>7/27</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Peter</td>

<td>WERNER</td>

<td>Cat 5A</td>

<td>10/27</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Scott</td>

<td>HARRINGTON</td>

<td>Cat 5A</td>

<td>12/27</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Tony</td>

<td>ZANON</td>

<td>Cat 5A</td>

<td>DNF</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td></td>

<td></td>

<td></td>

<td></td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Peter</td>

<td>WERNER</td>

<td>Cat 5B</td>

<td>4/28</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Michael</td>

<td>O'DONNELL</td>

<td>Cat 4A</td>

<td>3/41</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Jonathan</td>

<td>DOLLER</td>

<td>Cat 4A</td>

<td>8/41</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Brian</td>

<td>ALBERT</td>

<td>Cat 4A</td>

<td>9/41</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Algis</td>

<td>NORKEVICIUS</td>

<td>Cat 4A</td>

<td>16/41</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Nate</td>

<td>SIEVERS</td>

<td>Cat 4A</td>

<td>19/41</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Andrew</td>

<td>ROTHSTEIN</td>

<td>Cat 4A</td>

<td>20/41</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Michael</td>

<td>ROMAN</td>

<td>Cat 4A</td>

<td>24/41</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Adam</td>

<td>SHUTES</td>

<td>Cat 4A</td>

<td>33/41</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Jeffrey</td>

<td>LYDON</td>

<td>Cat 4A</td>

<td>37/41</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Kioko</td>

<td>MWOSA</td>

<td>Cat 4A</td>

<td>39/41</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Victor</td>

<td>MILLIGAN</td>

<td>Cat 4A</td>

<td>40/41</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Greg</td>

<td>NORTON</td>

<td>Cat 4A</td>

<td>41/41</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td></td>

<td></td>

<td></td>

<td></td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>ANDREW</td>

<td>ROTHSTEIN</td>

<td>Cat 4B</td>

<td>15/37</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td></td>

<td></td>

<td></td>

<td></td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Ari</td>

<td>SHOCKET</td>

<td>40+</td>

<td>3/38</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Bruce</td>

<td>PIERCE</td>

<td>40+</td>

<td>33/38</td>

</tr>

</tbody>

</table>

&nbsp;



&nbsp;]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>340</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-05-05 20:32:52</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-05-05 20:32:52</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>mount-blue-criterium</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Adam&#039;s Farm Short Track Series</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=370</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 14:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=370</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[The Adam's Farm Short Track Series kicks of on May 21st, <a href="https://www.bikereg.com/adams-farm-short-track-series">Register now on Bikereg.</a> The A Race will kick off at 6:00PM and the B Race will start at 6:35PM.



<h5 style="padding-bottom:8px">Check out the Short Track Teaser!</h5>

[vimeo clip_id=94829969 width=500]



&nbsp;



<h5 style="padding-bottom:8px">About Short Track Racing</h5>

Short track racing takes place on a short course (1.4miles) that is fast with very few technical challenges. The A Race is 30 minutes, while the B Race is 25 minutes. This series is set up as a training race and all races are open to anyone of any ability.



Typically, the A Race will be pros, cat 1s, and fast cat 2s. The B Race will typically be beginners, cat 3s, and new cat 2s. You may race both the A and B race in a single day for an extra workout. There are no prizes other than glory and bragging rights. Some races will have prizes for primes.



<h5>Honey bikes will be on site showing off their hand made bikes!</h5>

<a href="http://www.honeybikes.com/"><img alt="honey bikes" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/honey.png" width="100%" /></a>



<a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/Honey-Mountain-29er-Race.jpg"><img src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/Honey-Mountain-29er-Race.jpg" alt="Honey-Mountain-29er-Race" width="500" height="295" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-410" /></a>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>370</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-05-11 14:04:26</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-05-11 14:04:26</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>adams-farm-short-track-series</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Adam&#039;s Farm Short Track Series #1</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=412</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 11:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=412</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[In case you missed it this week, <a title="Dirt Wire" href="http://dirtwire.tv/">Dirt Wire TV</a> came out to shoot the first race in our Short Track Series.



[iframe id="viddler-f2a567e6" src="//www.viddler.com/embed/f2a567e6/?f=1&amp;offset=0&amp;autoplay=0&amp;player=full&amp;secret=84617477&amp;disablebranding=0&amp;view_secret=84617477" width="500" height="320" frameborder="0" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true" iframe]



&nbsp;

<table>

<tbody>

<tr>

<th></th>

<th align="left">

<h5>A RACE:</h5>

</th>

<th>

<h5>Points</h5>

</th>

<th></th>

<th align="left">

<h5>B RACE:</h5>

</th>

<th>

<h5>Points</h5>

</th>

</tr>

</tbody>

<tbody>

<tr>

<td style="padding-right: 8px">1

2

3

4

5

6

7

8

9

10</td>

<td style="padding-right: 8px">Charles Schubert

Jorma Mueller

Matt Sousa

Kevin Brant

Rich Pirro

Will Crissman

Tyler Eusden

Sean Willson

Jake Berry

Pete Werner</td>

<td>60

55

50

45

40

35

30

25

20

15</td>

<td style="padding-right: 8px">1

2

3

4

5

6

7

8

9

10</td>

<td style="padding-right: 8px">Curtis Chase

Whittle Ian

Peter Kuhn

Ted Myles

Mark Budreski

Tucker Walsh

BikeReg Guy (who knows who this is?)

Jessica Hughston

Marc Cedrone

John Fice</td>

<td>60

55

50

45

40

35

30

25

20

15</td>

</tr>

</tbody>

</table>

&nbsp;



Special thanks to our sponsors who are providing prizes for the over all points leaders. Landry's Bicycles, Bar Fly, Osmo Nutrition, Harpoon Brewery, ESI Grips, Flat Black Coffee, switchback Magazine, Cold Fusion Gelato.



See you in June for STXC #2 and don't forget about The Barn Burner on July 13th.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>412</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-05-23 11:24:21</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-05-23 11:24:21</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>adams-farm-short-track-series-1</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Gnar Weasels Shredeth  and Cyclonauts Racers Criterium </title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=445</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 19:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=445</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Michael O'Donnell and Jonathan Doller took 1st and 2nd place on the podium in the Mens 4/5 40+ at the Cyclonauts Racers Criterium last week. You can read Johnathan's account of how it went down <a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/forum/viewtopic.php?f=37&amp;t=111">here</a>



Kevin Brandt took 1st place in Sport 40-49 at the Gnar Weasels in Foxborough, MA!

<a style="padding-top: 10px" href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/brandt.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-447" alt="brandt" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/brandt.jpg" width="500" height="362" /></a>



If your not familar with the Gnar Weasels, check out the outtakes of the super gnarly part from <a href="http://dirtwire.tv"> dirtwire.tv</a>



[iframe id="viddler-2001e9b7" src="//www.viddler.com/embed/2001e9b7/?f=1&amp;offset=0&amp;autoplay=0&amp;player=full&amp;secret=71351299&amp;disablebranding=0&amp;view_secret=71351299" width="500" height="320" frameborder="0" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true" iframe]]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>445</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-06-02 19:53:32</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-06-02 19:53:32</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>blue-hills-finishes-may-on-the-podium</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Purgatory Road Race &amp; Massachusetts State Championships</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=457</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 14:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=457</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Adam Shutes with an impressive second place finish at the Purgatory Road Race &amp; Massachusetts State Championships



<a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/adam_purgatory.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-458" alt="adam_purgatory" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/adam_purgatory.jpg" width="500" height="312" /></a>

<table class="datatable1" width="100%">

<tbody>

<tr>

<td class="headerrow3" colspan="5">

<h5>Purgatory Road Race &amp; Massachusetts State Championships (Jun 8 2014)</h5>

</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td>Adam</td>

<td>Shutes</td>

<td>Men 4 35+</td>

<td width="70px">2 / 37</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow2">

<td>Mike</td>

<td>Morse</td>

<td>Men 5</td>

<td width="70px">9 / 73</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td>Christopher</td>

<td>Gibson</td>

<td>Men 5</td>

<td width="70px">17 / 73</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow2">

<td>William</td>

<td>Paredes</td>

<td>Men 5</td>

<td width="70px">42 / 73</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td>Alan</td>

<td>Potter</td>

<td>Masters 45+ (Cat 1-4)</td>

<td width="70px">22 / 53</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow2">

<td>Doug</td>

<td>Shepard</td>

<td>Masters 45+ (Cat 1-4)</td>

<td width="70px">39 / 53</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td>Ari</td>

<td>Shocket</td>

<td>Masters 35+ (Cat 1-4)</td>

<td width="70px">27 / 35</td>

</tr>

</tbody>

</table>

&nbsp;]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>457</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-06-09 14:28:08</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-06-09 14:28:08</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>podiums-in-purgatory</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Adam&#039;s Farm Short Track #2</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=469</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2014 18:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=469</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[We kicked the second Adam's Farm Short Track Training race this past Wednesday and had another awesome turnout! Pete MacLeod changed the course up a bit for this race. The laps were shorter but a little bit harder.



<a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/IMG_0226.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-471" alt="IMG_0226" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/IMG_0226.jpg" width="500" height="300" /></a>



&nbsp;

<table>

<tbody>

<tr>

<th></th>

<th align="left">

<h5>A RACE:</h5>

</th>

<th>

<h5>Points</h5>

</th>

<th></th>

<th align="left">

<h5>B RACE:</h5>

</th>

<th>

<h5>Points</h5>

</th>

</tr>

</tbody>

<tbody>

<tr>

<td style="padding-right: 8px">1

2

3

4

5

6

7

8

9

10</td>

<td style="padding-right: 8px">PJ Renquin

Will Chrissman

Jeff Fairbanks

Charlie Schubert

Eric Magnuson

Ian Odell

Jonathan Anderson

Rich Pirro

Ian Schon

Phil Golden</td>

<td>60

55

50

45

40

35

30

25

20

15</td>

<td style="padding-right: 8px">1

2

3

4

5

6

7

8

9

10</td>

<td style="padding-right: 8px">Sean Pantellere

Patrick Collins

Greg Colby

Ryan Aittaniemi

Chris Phenix

Matt Curtis

John Pell

Chris Canale

Todd Prekaski

Kent Hirshberg</td>

<td>60

55

50

45

40

35

30

25

20

15</td>

</tr>

</tbody>

</table>

&nbsp;

<h5>Series Totals:</h5>

&nbsp;

<table>

<tbody>

<tr>

<th></th>

<th align="left">

<h5>A RACE:</h5>

</th>

<th>

<h5>Points</h5>

</th>

<th></th>

<th align="left">

<h5>B RACE:</h5>

</th>

<th>

<h5>Points</h5>

</th>

</tr>

</tbody>

<tbody>

<tr>

<td style="padding-right: 8px">1

2

3

4

5

6

7

8

9

10

11

12

13

14

15

16

17

-

-

-</td>

<td style="padding-right: 8px">Charles Schubert

Will Crissman

Rich Pirro

PJ Renquin

Jorma Mueller

Matt Sousa

Jeff Fairbanks

Kevin Brant

Eric Magnuson

Ian Odell

Tyler Eusden

Jonathan Anderson

Sean Willson

Jake Berry

Ian Schon

Pete Werner

Phil Golden

-

-

-</td>

<td>105

90

65

60

55

50

50

45

40

35

30

30

25

20

20

15

15

-

-

-</td>

<td style="padding-right: 8px">1

2

3

4

5

6

7

8

9

10

11

12

13

14

15

16

17

18

19

20</td>

<td style="padding-right: 8px">Curtis Chase

Sean Pantellere

Whittle Ian

Patrick Collins

Peter Kuhn

Greg Colby

Ted Myles

Ryan Aittaniemi

Mark Budreski

Chris Phenix

Tucker Walsh

Matt Curtis

BikeReg Guy (who knows who this is?)

John Pell

Jessica Hughston

Chris Canale

Marc Cedrone

Todd Prekaski

John Fice

Kent Hirshberg</td>

<td>60

60

55

55

50

50

45

45

40

40

35

35

30

30

25

25

20

20

15

15</td>

</tr>

</tbody>

</table>

&nbsp;]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>469</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-06-20 18:23:42</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-06-20 18:23:42</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>adams-farm-short-track-2</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Rhode Island Masters&#039; Cycling Classic and the Hodges Village Damn Mountain Bike Race i</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=492</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 19:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=492</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[The Blue Hills squad is rolling into Summer strong! Ari Shocket started it off with a Win at the Rhode Island Masters' Cycling Classic in the 40+ Category.

<a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/Ari-Cash.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-493" alt="Ari Cash" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/Ari-Cash.jpg" width="500" height="316" /></a>



Philip Golden Followed it up with a Second Place CAT2 Finish at the Hodges Village Damn Mountain Bike Race in Oxford, MA. The Blue Hills Dirt Squad Represented in all 3 Categories this week.



<a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/Phil-Podium.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-494" alt="Phil Podium" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/Phil-Podium.jpg" width="499" height="279" /></a>

<table class="datatable1" width="100%">

<tbody>

<tr>

<td class="headerrow3" colspan="5">

<h5>Rhode Island Masters' Cycling Classic (Jun 21 2014)</h5>

</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Ari</td>

<td>Shocket</td>

<td>CAT 1-4 40-44 40k</td>

<td>1/5</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Ari</td>

<td>Shocket</td>

<td>CAT 1-4 40-44 20K</td>

<td>3/6</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>William</td>

<td>Paredes</td>

<td>CAT 5 45-49 20K</td>

<td>4/4</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Bob</td>

<td>Sherner</td>

<td>CAT 1-5 65-69</td>

<td>8/9</td>

</tr>

</tbody>

</table>

&nbsp;

<table>

<tbody>

<tr>

<td class="headerrow3" colspan="5">

<h5>The Keith Berger Memorial Criterium (Jun 22 2014)</h5>

</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Austin</td>

<td>Guyette</td>

<td>CAT 3/4</td>

<td>60/66</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Austin/</td>

<td>Guyette</td>

<td>CAT 4/5</td>

<td>7/62</td>

</tr>

</tbody>

</table>

&nbsp;

<table>

<tbody>

<tr>

<td class="headerrow3" colspan="5">

<h5>Hodges Village Damn Mountain Bike Race (June 22, 2014)</h5>

</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Pete</td>

<td>Werner</td>

<td>CAT 1 30-39</td>

<td>7/10</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Philip</td>

<td>Golden</td>

<td>CAT 2 40-49</td>

<td>2/15</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Jeff</td>

<td>Muldoon</td>

<td>CAT 2 30-39</td>

<td>9/10</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Ted</td>

<td>Myles</td>

<td>CAT 3 40-49</td>

<td>8/15</td>

</tr>

<tr>

<td>Richard</td>

<td>Walsh</td>

<td>CAT 3 50+</td>

<td>5/5</td>

</tr>

</tbody>

</table>

&nbsp;]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>492</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-06-24 19:03:02</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-06-24 19:03:02</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>rolling-into-summer-strong</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>The Barn Burner</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=513</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 11:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=513</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[The second annual Barn Burner Mountain Bike Race went under way this past Sunday. Thanks to all of the volunteers, Landry's Bicycles, Pedro's, Osmo Nutrition, ESI Grips, Dancing Deer Baking Co, Bar Fly, Harpoon Brewery, Teddie Peanut Butter, Mad Alchemy Embrocation, switchback Magazine, Flat Black Coffee, Cold Fusion Gelato, and Charles River Running, for providing unreal prizes and awesome race day support.



Check out the post race interviews and video highlights  at <a href="http://dirtwire.tv/events/the-barn-burner/">Dirtwire TV</a>.  Check out the Race Results on the <a href="http://root66raceseries.com/RT66/Results.html">Root 66 Webpage</a>



&nbsp;

<h3>The Barn Burner- Highlights</h3>

&nbsp;



[iframe id="viddler-3c7f41fd" src="//www.viddler.com/embed/3c7f41fd/?f=1&amp;offset=0&amp;autoplay=0&amp;player=full&amp;secret=11610842&amp;disablebranding=0&amp;view_secret=11610842" width="500" height="320" frameborder="0" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true" iframe]



&nbsp;

<h3>The Rock Garden Uncut!</h3>

&nbsp;



[iframe id="viddler-9f5a75e3" src="//www.viddler.com/embed/9f5a75e3/?f=1&amp;offset=0&amp;autoplay=0&amp;player=full&amp;secret=76862013&amp;disablebranding=0&amp;view_secret=76862013" width="500" height="320" frameborder="0" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true" iframe]]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>513</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-07-17 11:12:33</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-07-17 11:12:33</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>the-barn-burner</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Adam&#039;s Farm Short Track # 3</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=537</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2014 22:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=537</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<span style="line-height: 1.5">[iframe id="viddler-3b8433f1" src="//www.viddler.com/embed/3b8433f1/?f=1&amp;offset=0&amp;autoplay=0&amp;player=full&amp;secret=46655778&amp;disablebranding=0&amp;view_secret=46655778" width="500" height="320" frameborder="0" mozallowfullscreen="true" webkitallowfullscreen="true" iframe]</span>



&nbsp;

<table>

<tbody>

<tr>

<th></th>

<th align="left">

<h5>A RACE:</h5>

</th>

<th>

<h5>POINTS</h5>

</th>

<th></th>

<th align="left">

<h5>B RACE:</h5>

</th>

<th>

<h5>POINTS</h5>

</th>

</tr>

</tbody>

<tbody>

<tr>

<td>1

2

3

4

5

6

7

8

9

10</td>

<td>Levi Kurlander

Tyler Eusden

Charles Schubert

Rich Pirro

Jeff Fairbanks

John Golden

Phil Golden

Alexi Arapoff

Mark Budreski

Cory Johananessen</td>

<td>60

55

50

45

40

35

30

25

20

15</td>

<td>1

2

3

4

5

6

7

8

9

10</td>

<td>Michael Condon

Tucker Walsh

Ben Larivirse

Peter Kuhn

Todd Prekaski

John Steiger

George Lester

Chris Canale

Michele Smith

Chris Golden</td>

<td>60

55

50

45

40

35

30

25

20

15</td>

</tr>

</tbody>

</table>

&nbsp;

<h5>Series Totals:</h5>

&nbsp;

<table>

<tbody>

<tr>

<th></th>

<th align="left">

<h5>A RACE:</h5>

</th>

<th>

<h5>POINTS</h5>

</th>

<th></th>

<th align="left">

<h5>B RACE:</h5>

</th>

<th>

<h5>POINTS</h5>

</th>

</tr>

</tbody>

<tbody>

<tr>

<td>1

2

3

4

5

6

7

8

9

10

11

12

13

14

15

16

17

18

19

20

21

22

-

-

-

-</td>

<td>Charles Schubert

Rich Pirro

Jeff Fairbanks

Will Crissman

Tyler Eusden

Levi Kurlander

PJ Renquin

Jorma Mueller

Matt Sousa

Phil Golden

Kevin Brant

Eric Magnuson

John Golden

Ian Odell

Jonathan Anderson

Alexi Arapoff

Sean Willson

Mark Budreski

Jake Berry

Ian Schon

Cory Johananessen

Pete Werner

-

-

-

-</td>

<td>155

110

90

90

85

60

60

55

50

45

45

40

35

35

30

25

25

20

20

20

15

15

-

-

-

-</td>

<td>1

2

3

4

5

6

7

8

9

10

11

12

13

14

15

16

17

18

19

20

21

22

23

24

25

26</td>

<td>Peter Kuhn

Tucker Walsh

Curtis Chase

Sean Pantellere

Todd Prekaski

Michael Condon

Whittle Ian

Patrick Collins

Greg Colby

Chris Canale

Ben Larivirse

Ted Myles

Ryan Aittaniemi

Mark Budreski

Chris Phenix

Matt Curtis

John Steiger

BikeReg Guy (who knows who this is?)

John Pell

George Lester

Jessica Hughston

Marc Cedrone

Michele Smith

John Fice

Kent Hirshberg

Chris Golden</td>

<td>95

90

60

60

60

60

55

55

50

50

50

45

45

40

40

35

35

30

30

30

25

20

20

15

15

15</td>

</tr>

</tbody>

</table>

&nbsp;]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>537</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-07-28 22:39:04</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-07-28 22:39:04</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>adams-farm-short-track-3</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Pan-Mass Challenge</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=549</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2014 14:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=549</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[The Blue Hills Cycling Club would like to Congratulate Bobby Allen, Steven Fish, John Moore, Steve O’Connell, John Peterson, Joe Roach, Dylan Sanders, Sean Saganey, James Scott and Bill Zucker for their participation in this year’s Pan-Mass Challenge.



&nbsp;



<a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/pan-mass.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-551" alt="pan-mass" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/pan-mass.jpg" width="500" height="375" /></a>



&nbsp;



The Pan-Mass Challenge raises money for life-saving cancer research and treatment at Dana-Farber Cancer Institute through an annual bike-a-thon that crosses the Commonwealth of Massachusetts. Since its founding in 1980, the PMC has successfully melded support from committed cyclists, volunteers, corporate sponsors and individual contributors. All are essential to the PMC's goal and model: to attain maximum fundraising efficiency while increasing its annual gift.



&nbsp;



<a href="http://www.pmc.org/sites/pmc.org/files/backgrounds/unrestrictedgiving.pdf">Click here to learn more about how Dana-Farber uses PMC funds.</a>



&nbsp;]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>549</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-08-05 14:03:03</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-08-05 14:03:03</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>pan-mass-challenge</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Blue Hills Mountain Biking</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=566</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 18:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=566</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h5>Gearing up for some long days in the Saddle</h5>

The Blue Hills MTB Squad has been gearing up for some long days in the saddle. Good luck to the riders heading to the Hampshire 100, Root 66 Marathon Series and the Vermont 50.



[iframe src="//player.vimeo.com/video/103133317" width="500" height="281" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen iframe]

<h5>All aboard the Pain Train!</h5>

Team Rider Scott Taylor Dreams about the intervals he could have been doing on his Road Bike!



<a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/paintrain.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-578" alt="paintrain" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/paintrain.jpg" width="500" height="281" /></a>



&nbsp;



&nbsp;]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>566</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-08-11 18:48:35</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-08-11 18:48:35</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>blue-hills-mountain-biking</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Tokeneke Classic Road Race</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=585</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 12:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=585</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[The road team represented the club well this past weekend at the Tokeneke Classic Road Race  Congratulations to Adam Shutes on another top 10 finish on an extremely tough course with over 4,000 ft of climbing!



<a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/token.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-588" alt="token" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/token.jpg" width="500" height="375" /></a>

<table class="datatable1" width="100%">

<tbody>

<tr>

<td class="headerrow3" colspan="5">

<h5>Tokeneke Classic Road Race (Aug 10 2014)</h5>

</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td>Adam</td>

<td>Shutes</td>

<td>Men 4 35+</td>

<td width="70px">7/51</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow2">

<td>William</td>

<td>Paredes</td>

<td>Men 5</td>

<td width="70px">42 / 73</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td>Alan</td>

<td>Potter</td>

<td>40+</td>

<td width="70px">15 / 35</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td>Austin</td>

<td>Guyette</td>

<td>Men 4 u35</td>

<td width="70px">15 / 24</td>

</tr>

</tbody>

</table>

&nbsp;]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>585</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-08-12 12:22:11</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-08-12 12:22:11</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>tokeneke-classic-road-race</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Millstone Grind Mountain Bike Race</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=594</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 18:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=594</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[
		
		
		<p>Pete MacLeod and Pete Werner headed to Websterville. VT this past week to race in the Root66 Millstone Grind XC Mountain Bike Race. If you haven't been to this race, the course is awesome, lots of roots, lots of flow and a nice long 8 mile lap. Entry fee to the race included a an excellent post race meal and beer, with choices from BHCC Club Spenser Harpoon Brewery and the Alchemist's Heady Topper.



Light rain began to fall a few hours before the race and ended just before the begining of the Pro/CAT1 races transforming the race into a very technically challenging event.</p>



<a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/Millstone.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-595" alt="Millstone" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/Millstone.jpg" width="500" height="482" /></a>

<table class="datatable1" width="100%">

<tbody>

<tr>

<td class="headerrow3" colspan="5">

<h5>Millstone Grind Cross Country Mountain Bike Race (Aug 17, 2014)</h5>

</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td>Pete</td>

<td>MacLeod</td>

<td>Mens Pro/CAT1 Open</td>

<td width="70px">5/10</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow2">

<td>Pete</td>

<td>Werner</td>

<td>Mens CAT 1 30-39</td>

<td width="70px">3/4</td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td></td>

<td></td>

<td></td>

<td width="70px"></td>

</tr>

<tr class="datarow1">

<td></td>

<td></td>

<td></td>

<td width="70px"></td>

</tr>

</tbody>

</table>

&nbsp;



&nbsp;]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>594</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-08-18 18:00:38</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-08-18 18:00:38</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>millstone-grind-mountain-bike-race</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
				<title>Hampshire 100 Mountain Bike Race</title>
		<link>http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=600</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 18:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pedro]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.bluehillscycling.com/?p=600</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Scott Taylor and Ted Myles tackled a very slippery, muddy and rocky Hampshire 100k this past weekend with over 7,800 feet of Climbing.  Scott crushed the entire Sport field by over 9 minutes for a top Spot on the Podium and Ted busted out a 10th place spot on the Novice Podium!



<h5>Scott Taylor Pictured Below with his First Place Wind Chimes</h5>

<a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/20140817_162323_resized.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-601" alt="20140817_162323_resized" src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/20140817_162323_resized.jpg" width="500" height="281" /></a>





<h5>Ted Myles on the Podium </h5>

<a href="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/Ted.jpg"><img src="http://www.bluehillscycling.com/BHCC-3/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/Ted.jpg" alt="Ted" width="500" height="281" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-604" /></a>]]></content:encoded>
		